I know
Yeah, and then yeah, and then he like you know, he has all this hate in his heart, right?
I know it wasn't you it wasn't you this time Joe, but you know, you know about I think
I didn't kick him off tonight, but I had to kick him off last I mean it's like
It's pretty odd. I mean it's like really obvious and it's like what's really weird is like
There's no there's like no, we're like all day. Oh, what a cute dog that there's no context at all for like
Well, the dog needs to protect I know maybe Joe. They see maybe you were saying stuff Joe. I don't know cuz then he's like
but he's just
You know yours. It's not
What happened I'll
Rogue no man showed a firearm on the chat
Or on the live panel
Okay, I mean, I mean, you know
Alex knows something good, but I've explained to Alex even I mean, it's like it's so hard so guys just like I
Might have to just stop having panels
I just like I don't know it's like or just have to give the link to like specific people and like you have to like
Go through the like I'll have gatekeepers for the and you have to just know them to be able to go in the pan
I'll have to be I'll have to be more exclusive. It's like I think it's I'm you know, I know if you need like a little bit more
Say I just can't keep letting it everyone off the street, especially now it's like that that would just be like
Not pretty smart
You understand robo, but you have big knees that way. I mean we all like yeah
I but first of all if even if you do have that you're not gonna don't show it don't don't lay all your cards out of it
Oh, here's exactly what I have you know, it's like then they know okay
Well, it's more bull profess that night when I you know, so it's like you know, you just you pretend like you have like a
Mote around here. Yeah, I am mode. I got a castle. I mean that's like you can say all that
Rogues in on it to Alex. Oh my gosh. Yeah, so I Alex look so I mean I might need to be taking Alex seriously now
Okay, hold on me guys. It's just only take an hour. She I just think I have to get Joe's the theories on who's who hold on
Okay, so Joe can you can you just work ban Joe? Oh, no, I mean Alex is there Alex? I didn't hear the theory. Okay, so
so Tony is
Crucible ghosts
Is he flirty diamond or is he?
This is because I'm sorry because computer only looking okay, so roguro man's not okay, so and you said rain is the leader
God he is like you got you said God he's just like it's coffee for them or something that's kind of I
Would think God he would be the leader
Okay, why he yeah, he is he's he's ghost of out AMC, but I don't think he's I don't know if he's there
I don't know they sound similar
But he's okay, but also I'm gonna put down school of Afton's is Alex because that's another theory and it's just as viable as other ones
I've never seen you in the same room together if this you know at the same time. I'm only heard your voices
You have two phones on who knows right?
AI is getting crazy
Joe got it and ain't
one
Protestant
They I like that. You're saying the Mormons. You're saying the Mormons. I mean, it's like come on. I
Don't think so. Have you heard of wasps at WASP
Big Nisha they are man that man flirty diamond reads me makes me really uncomfortable. I'm sorry
Okay, no, so Alex, here's the here's a big question. Who is Big Nisha? Okay?
I know this is she's not like a 500 pound
African-American woman in Louisiana with a son named Donnell
That's gay that is in BKG that has a BKG tattoo that he just got even though he's 16
And she's getting in my cat and he reads terror at the mall. I mean, I mean, it's a very it's more
Detailed lower than my own lore and it's my show, but who's who's a who's big my issue guys. Tell me that
Don't be offended big Mike. Nice. Yeah, don't be offended. Okay, I'm just asking
But I Google I I do the Google reverse image search nation and it came back to Big Mama's house
It's just a picture of Tyler Perry in an outfit I
Figured you had a long time ago. Nisha. Okay, but I still like you. Okay
Okay, guys. Okay, so maybe I will post the link
The real account
Oh, it's a soccer. I'm sorry soccer count
Yeah, and likes I guess like a dirty sock. It stinks a little bit
Don't know about you big Nisha. You need to send some of your driver's license or something
Verify no, you don't have to okay, so I posted a link
Your name is Donny check Carter. Oh, you're related to JZ by chance. I think his last name is Carter, too
It's okay. I'm just gonna be a hard time. You can be whoever you want to be. Oh
I
Just got okay. Thank you. I got I got I thank you for the cash out. Okay, so
So, well, I wrote down when you have to wait backstage for you. I talked to the panel
Definitely us violation that could get my account deleted and then what would happen you just like laugh and or something like that
And I'd be I'd be you know shit out of luck, right?
So do you understand like what your actions, especially when you're on my panel?
This is like my house kind of it's like your actions will have consequences not for you necessarily all I can do is kick you out
but they'll have consequences for me and I don't you don't care about me and so why would I even like
entertain you here I do care about you so I think that you misunderstand me for being so malicious
which I'm not in any way whatsoever well you but you don't understand you're not supposed to show
firearms on live I mean it's like maybe I didn't explain that I never saw the firearm no no no no
And I have done it in the past in other panels and there's been no problem whatsoever, so I was not aware that it will be such a problem at all.
So
How do you know how you lost your wrench again? How'd you lose your wrench Alex? I took your wrench away Alex
What did you do? I mean, it's like very dangerous
No, I was if I took it away again, I just have to
Can you do you have a fucking backbone Joe?
Because whatever whoever hosts you you're gonna adapt to whatever they want you to say any fucking day
What are you okay about you need to be in a mental hospital because it sounds like
And of course and then you you you'll be in the
I need to be in a mental hospital of course. I haven't written down rogue. No, man
I'm gonna write down rogue. No math. I don't write down
But I'll go back all you have next year all you have next your name is you say you have like a little get little x
Yes, you have a strike on my channel like it like it's like from from you know
I know but as I say happy birthday to you then you then you said terrible things on piano. I mean
The reason they want a wrench is because the they can check everyone's channel, which is not cool
Well, I mean you should mean genuine mods should be able to check the channel make sure that they're not just a
You know just start your channel just the troll here
Yeah, I mean, but it's like, yeah, I don't need like, you know, there's too much investigation
to go on for everybody in this chance to give a job for an army of private detectives to
figure out this chat.
So it doesn't let them bother.
I was not even going to go down that road.
Are you talking to yourself again, Mike?
Are you talking to yourself again?
because I'll tell you right now, you're the sexiest guy I've ever played with.
Really? Wow. Wow, Joe.
What's up? What's your question?
I'm not saying I'm gay, but if I were quite lucky, I'd be like, I wouldn't have sex with that guy.
You went so far right now.
Joe, I feel harassed by you. I feel harassed by you. I feel harassed by you. I feel harassed by you.
I'm really a fan.
I feel harassed you.
Put it down a little bit.
Yeah, rub your hair.
three Z here Joe's just taking it too far
Wow
Yeah
Yeah, but this is this but this way like I'll be able to like when I write down everyone's name in this book
And then it's like and I'll break down if they're a mod or remember and then I'll be able to like
Note those things as I'm if they do something egregious
I'll take some of that stuff into account.
Somebody in the chat made a good point.
Remember that song by Chicago?
That was like 12, five, six, seven, four.
Thank you, I don't remember that one, but I remember this song
Looking kind of done with her finger and her thumb and her forehead
I think Joe is a saboteur.
I think Joe is trying to correct me.
What about very naked ladies?
I want to see, I want to see, I want to see your, I want to see your bear naked ladies go with everything he's saying.
It makes me really uncomfortable.
Hey, Electra, you want to sing that?
Yep.
Did Electra's hear?
I like that.
Yeah, it was.
That wasn't me.
That was Alex's voice.
Hey, Alex, don't, don't, don't mock me.
That was me.
That was actually my voice.
Joe is making everybody very uncomfortable.
You're seeing with me. You're seeing with me. You're seeing with me. You're seeing with me. You're seeing with me. You're seeing with me. You're seeing with me. You're seeing with me. You're seeing with me. You're seeing with me. You're seeing with me. You're seeing with me. You're seeing with me. You're seeing with me. You're seeing with me. You're seeing with me. You're seeing with me. You're seeing with me. You're seeing with me. You're seeing with me. You're seeing with me. You're seeing with me. You're seeing with me. You're seeing with me. You're seeing with me. You're seeing with me. You're seeing with me. You're seeing with me. You're seeing with me. You're seeing with me. You're seeing with me. You're seeing with me. You're seeing with me. You're seeing with me. You're seeing with me. You're seeing with me. You're seeing with me. You
Joe, you're on your last little leg in this chance.
If I kick you out, you're listening.
Look at all these things about what we've been.
I don't want to live tomorrow.
I just want to live where I belong.
It's my loss.
What the fuck, Joe?
What the fuck?
Oh, it's like a broken highway.
Yeah, that I did it my way.
I don't want to live where I belong.
I just want to shit on Oliver.
Do you hear those words?
Thank you.
Oh, what the?
Fuck, what the hell was there?
Oh my God, I can not believe Joe said that shame on him.
You're making everybody uncomfortable.
You're making everybody not want to join this channel.
No, nobody's nobody.
No, no, no, no, Rogue, you can just take my lead.
It is what the same to say.
I mean, it's like, I'll have someone else when you don't need to.
All right.
If I'm making a put a cock emoji in the chat, if I'm making your
contour or put a broken heart, if I'm rogue, no, man, it's making you uncomfortable.
Oh, so.
That's what I was and if I'm making you uncomfortable just put just put a banana in the chat. Okay. No, it's like you hell
No, you're looking my best friend man. Hell. No, you're not you are the best friend of Joe. Oh
My god
This guy knows everything. Sorry, man. Who are guys who else was there?
Guys who went to me tell me you want your name in the book guys
Just tell me what your name in the book could be immortalized in my my history of my show
I don't doc's home. I don't
have his home
Well, no, I mean nobody really shouldn't like I mean unless we have a reason to like you know ray one is like somebody on an
Alls whoever just said Joe. Yeah. Yeah, I know I know because I thought I thought you know
They don't have balls to tell me I thought I thought it was I thought it was like this guy Ray
I know
Joe you are gay
OK. It's OK. It's OK. Be gay is OK.
Be gay is OK, but he said that he didn't have the balls.
Well, it's okay. You can you know, I'm actually you can transition gay. What's wrong with that man?
He's gonna transition into it. No, he doesn't wrong with it, but Joe's
Transitions over I'm actually a woman. Joe's transitioning into he's turning into a unit. He's turning to a unicorn not a
Like she's doing really good tonight. If you talk to me be like she's a good guy
So Joe finish his transition. Congratulations Joe
I
Physicians rogue I bet you're really good at getting to your positions. You're fucking creep on at least I'm feeling like
You tricked us on to believing that you were you never heard of corn you never heard of corn
I
Got everything one of us, and you don't understand the pain you know, okay
Okay, okay, so Joe
To know I mean, I don't know
I'm gonna be less annoying than what's going on
My boys how my best friend doing I love all you
you know I love fucking Shafely aka Ziggy I love Rob Nomek Mr. Gunn Shower and you know Saiki's my boy
what your boyfriend has something to do yet yeah my boyfriend my girlfriend my boyfriend everything
why are you saying those things what the fuck it's okay you can say that you can say that
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't
You're not you're a form bomber. You're a fucking protestant from hell. You don't like psyche
What is wrong with you, bro? I am ziggie. You're right. I am ziggie. I am ziggie. I am 100%
Bro, you don't gotta tell me. I am him. I'm giving you no shit and you're more than ziggie
Which is great
Alex, so it's the internet it's the internet so so so if Alex wants to come on as
Alright, so if Joe wants to come under a punky Brewster account calm so punky Brewster, if you want
You guys got psyche brain wash
Do you remember Peewee Herman's big adventures like that's one of my favorite movies when you
You large Marge. What the hell are you in that story?
more attention X's large mark that woman Tracy X's large March Alex Alex or Alex would be more like
he'd be like
You know, he'd be like the cop that pulls over Pee Wee and then Pee Wee dresses like a woman
We got damn it. You leave me alone. Yeah, you're Pee Wee. I'm the chubby fuck look the first bike
That's you know, my Francis is sold the bike I say you look a
He gets pulled over by this he gets pulled over by a cop and the cops like let's
Francis black gum remember when Francis had to eat his black gum and he gave him the black gum and he ate it
He's like a hot Francis you bitch
When I'm working we saved the pet store
Naked and then he like
Save the pet story mother fucker
Is carrying the snakes out
But he carried the snakes out of that pet store. I fucking love that movie
It's in the back to the future that one
I don't even need your like words like so you just shut the fuck up
What about at the end when he was watching it and cooking mr. Herman?
page in Mr. Merman, you have a powerful foal at the front desk.
Yep.
They really do that.
They dub voices.
Okay.
I know.
I heard you.
Well, yeah
That's drugs that's drugs though
No, look what happened all the way Alex fake cop and gay somebody I'm not getting Chad's like Alex fake
All right. No, what's the game? Yeah, I agree. You ever said that right?
I
Pretty sure I don't want to smell it
Should we Alex? No, we want to smell like it. So you do
Under the covers like
He wants to smell my
Actually a shower to get a shower. I don't want I don't want to come on the way back. Oh my god
Do you remember John Lieberman psyche? You remember John Lieberman? Yeah, John from Howard Stern. Yes
He did use the guy who did Langford you never any crowned
Yes, you remember Joe should be saying the craziest things that you have to restart your panel
And let's unless that needs to happen. I don't even want to hear those words. I don't I like don't say it
Let's just pretend like
It was my fault. It's my fault. I talked too much inside baseball about my show like because it's like you're not supposed to know
What's the show you're supposed to like? Oh, here's on YouTube with this guy. No, you're not supposed to know
Any of the any of the drama I I told too much of a way I told you away
But it's like I don't want it to be like the drama is not about my channel. It's just my channel
the way the drama is delivered. So it's like suing the post office.
Yeah. Well, big waste of time. Okay. So, hey, DJ Lecture out.
We just did the Riley Martin show. Oh, I love Riley Martin. I just like, I thought he was just
Did you just see my worst nightmare? Oh, I like Riley Martin. Hi, baby.
Did I see Rudy? Hold on. I'm just saying hi to Jamie's Cowboys. Oh, look at those little whiskers.
Love you little cat. Oh look at it. I mean, that's love man. I miss my dog. That is love. I
Don't care anymore
I don't even care. What are you talking about? So pay pay son and chief spectra be a big cage here
I don't know what that means. Okay. It says the only that makes sense. So shit, but you don't care about life
I get it. Yeah. Members are here again here
Especially when you're kissing that thing. Is that your mom or your girlfriend? What is that thing? I
Don't know about that. I don't know about that
of the
one of the
My fucking great grandma the other day. I'm asking a question. Who the hell was that?
That's that's his girlfriend
I'm gonna say next time she's here you gotta talk to her like that you gotta say she's
You're not gonna be doing that because first of all, you know, we don't talk to people like that on my show
Okay, we're not gonna do that. He's a coward. He's a second of all, you're not gonna talk over me out on my show
Okay, you're not gonna like be have a louder mic than me and talk over me. I'm just all I have the backstage powers
I can just put you backstage and it's heavy. There's longer than I want. There you go
You go cop face. You just you just say you see it patrol the green room for a while. Okay. Talk to the chat, okay?
I mean, Alex, clean the bathrooms in the backstage.
Clean the bathrooms up, you little bum, while you're backstage.
Alex, clean the bathrooms up, you bum, you loudmouth.
I'm Alex, I work for the cops.
Nigga, you are a cop, you little bum.
Thank you, Suggie.
I don't know what's happening tonight guys. I mean, it's like jeez
We're just having a nice nice show. Oh, he's already backstage naked. I mean Alex come on the pre-coast not starting till
I be and Jamie how is everybody so I did I
Guys so I'm right guys I'm writing
This book it says be home better screen. It says be kind. Okay, so this is my my the rulebook for my show
It's I mean, it's really rulebook. It'll be like a notebook
I'll open it up. Open it up. Open it up. What's this man? The first page. Oh, I I mean
I had others have written here. It has like Hebrew and stuff in it. It has like some what does it say?
What does it say? It says
Fourteen significant spiritual precepts are discussed in the Zohar. So it's about Kabbalah. I was writing it says the first
Precept to be an awe of the Creator
Develop true attachment and connections with the light of the Creator
Fear awe is a gateway to enter the world of faith
Fundamental fear is fear of omnipotent master. All that exists is nothing compared to the Creator of all
This is you want to hear more?
Yeah, I wouldn't hear more. I wouldn't hear more. Okay. This is second
So second precepts love the Creator unconditional and a great love includes both aspects of kindness
Plus judgment. Okay third precept
Constant awareness of the Creator. No in a Almighty Creator rules the world. Okay fourth precept
Knowing that all is unified
Hashem is the Elohim
Okay, how about how about yeah, okay, and it says it's precept steady of the beat is joined earlier
That was cool and beat it came up early. Yeah, that was cool. It was fun. It was fun. Oh, it was fun
She's my pet down now
So baby, yeah, there's 14 precepts. I have right now, but this is they're from the Zohar
There's a book called the Zohar if you study Kabbalah, it is not for everybody to
I mean, it's probably I mean I according to traditional duties, and I would probably not be loud within 20 feet of it
but
You know they changed the rules up a little bit, but you know traditionally you were supposed to be like a man over 40
Jamie says and not aware anyone trying to make
is through a day you can do it, you're beautiful.
Anyone that makes a make it through a day that you can,
you're beautiful and positive.
Get your healing, vibes, prayers on the way.
Oh, you're an angel.
That's an angel right there.
Are you talking to me?
You are my angel, you are my angel, you are my angel, you are my angel, you are my angel, you are my angel, you are my angel, you are my angel, you are my angel, you are my angel, you are my angel, you are my angel, you are my angel, you are my angel, you are my angel, you are my angel, you are my angel, you are my angel, you are my angel, you are my angel, you are my angel, you are my angel, you are my angel, you are my angel, you are my angel, you are my angel, you are my angel, you are my angel, you are my angel, you are my angel, you are my angel, you are my angel, you are my angel, you are my angel, you are my angel, you are my angel, you are my angel, you are my angel, you are my angel, you are my angel, you are my angel, you are my angel, you are my angel, you are my angel, you are my
Okay, well, you won't you won't just dream with your eyes open and you won't miss a thing
Okay, so Irby fatal you are you're a man. You're a mother
I look like my eyes are open or my eyes cross the
Really they look they look they look they look a bit raccoon ish and and small
Got it almost like I mean, I'm just I'm just I'm very honest person
Okay, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
and your fantasies.
I remember it well.
Alex, oh, look at me, I'm Alex.
You're Pete.
Okay, so I'm gonna write down the names
as I see them coming through.
I just, but I make sure they're at least like that.
I know them.
I ask you what you write down in your book,
write, Joe is the most handsome guy
I've ever laid my eyes on.
Write that in your fucking book.
be like wow is that guy like hot as hell or fucking or my eyes crooked I can write
Instead of doing that. I can write in your name. I said parentheses. I'm like you're right Brad Pitt
I can write not call me so horror. I got all right. Not so horrible. Is that okay?
If I were just right call me Brad Pitt stains. I want to be called Brad Pitt stains
Okay
well
Thank you. I want to hear a dinner and I want to hear Jennifer Aniston called him when she was mad at him
That's what I'll call you. Okay. Oh, Joe Rancid. I'll take a bucket. Jennifer. And Jennifer and Jennifer Aniston
I'm jewelry. Oh, Jennifer Aniston
She's sexy as hell. Yeah, I'm ready. Erby fatal and I'm writing
Hey, I was a moderator up a mod. What why are you mental?
Who else wants to be in the book?
Who wants to be in the book or you can suggest you can suggest a page. I'll give you a page in the book, but it's like, you know
Anyone a line in the book, but the whole page
What is that even mean is like what is the milk man? Oh, yeah, so the milk man the paper boy, so those are predictable things
But but but the mailman but the mailman is still around and they still deliver mail
Just like they have for a hundred year like what so that's what happens. You know nothing. I'm a milkman
Boy, there's even a milk. They even the milk even the milk man's around still
I mean, it's like, you know, he he has a few more kids
You're saying you asked thanks for Carl Winslow. Wow. Thanks a lot. No, you know, that's that's Alex
Alex Alex is Alex the Carl Winslow. He's like the black cop
You said it Alex your car wins look and you're you're your uncle you're your your uncle Joe you can be your cool
You can be like yeah
Is the phone our Cal yeah, so you got a key or you think I do that?
Yeah
So anyway, oh my god
Gosh guys, you guys ain't getting it by the way, thanks a lot rogue nomad and Joe
Thank you so much because I like 60 people to chat now
There's like 20 people like guys it hurts my show it hurts everything when I have to start over so stop
Like please like just behave yourself in the test. I don't have to
with me and Alex showing you got up like five viewers hell yeah no no no no there were five
viewers left in the chat when you got what you guys got up here and everyone just flees the room
oh you're saying we took people away are yes well no no it's like it's but you know when I had to
end the stream and then everyone gets together and then they find the news stream or let's say oh
that he's that guy's too much trouble he just has a bunch of psychos on his panel and I don't feel
comfortable with that
You're one Super Bowl 35 Alex the Baltimore Ravens kick the Giants ass in Super Bowl 35. I'm a Giants fan
I'm not saying I've elephant tightest
I've got a really big year, but yeah, but your cock is like
Just saying man
It's misshapen and and unhealthy looking
It looks it looks like a drag gooey duck or something like that. I don't know. I'm gonna describe it earlier
I will throw a fucking whatever you just said it looks like a drag gooey duck
Dragon drag gooey duck, you know what a gooey duck is
You haven't heard of the GUI?
You can name five Hobbits, name four Hobbits right now from Lord of the Rings, or can you?
Frodo, Frodo, Bilbo, Dildo, Helga, and Rex, I don't know.
What are the names?
I got these two of them.
Is it Bilbo?
I don't know.
I'm going to show you a picture of a GUI duck.
Hold on, I'm going to show you a picture.
Show me a picture of Beatas nipples. Please. Oh
What the fuck is that a permit crap? It's a guy. What the hell am I looking at? It's ha it's a it's called a
Renting hanging out. What the fuck are those little things?
I think those I think that's I think there's a sperm or something here here like here's a picture of you Alex
God what the hell is that what the fuck am I looking at is that Frankenstein looks like Frankenstein?
No, it's a you bite you down on the beach, and it's like and then it like it actually will squirt like a big thing of semen and like water
Because he looks like he wants to suck that he wants
It looks like one of those hands you put on your hand at the baseball game and they say hey
I'm number one doesn't look like that kind of look like a shoe though. What do you guys think?
Yeah, this one this guy found a big one he found a big gooey duck. Oh my god
Little goo, okay, and it says let me see if it says it says it says the product gooey duck or the
Yeah, yeah, it's like a it's like a mollusk, but it's like
As it smells like you know like
I don't know
Like Alex's unshamed fucking balls. That's what it's about. Oh my god
Oh my god
Where is he left but look how disgusting that is look how disgusting it looks like it
It's like it has a dog. Oh
It has a dog's lipstick. What is that red the red red you coming out? It's horrible
It's like a dog's lipstick. You know the dog's lipstick
Okay, everyone laugh people laughing. That's it the discord brigade. Oh, yeah
Okay, guys, okay, please don't get a gang war tonight. I don't remember the lyrics to
Officer Krumky or whatever the fuck where they see in West side story home West side story. What do they say?
Remember the lyrics to don't go check
Yeah, I know that some but I'm trying to like
Are you holding your phone with nine fingers like how many fingers do you have like wow?
Like I'm I'm fingers right. I'm like I'm like Eric the midget my fingers are also used to gather and use
Bye for now
Goodbye for now. Uh, let me see was that what's his story? What's what's on hold? No, yeah officer
Okay, so what's his what's his story songs? I'll tell you what the song was called
It's not officer crumpy. That's kind of like
Ralph the case yeah, do you think I think he was Ralph was like he was he had a very gay personality where everyone thought he was gay
But then he was like a total like
Pig, but I think he's kind of like the Andy dick
Oh
What do you guys your mind your mind's about to be blown guys, so I remember how it keeps
You know how I keep saying my show's West Side Story?
Listen to this.
It says, in West Side Story, the character's son
you may be referring to is Tony, who is the former member
of the Jets gang and falls in love with Maria,
the sister of Bernardo, the leader of the Sharks.
Tony's character is a central feature in the story,
experiencing a compassionate love,
or passionate love affair,
and ultimately facing tragic consequences.
Uh-oh, uh-oh.
I'm glad I'm not that Tony. I'm more like the I'm more like the fucking
I'm just like
Look at this fucking arms. Look at this fucking. Look at this good
Do you save that that orange buzz off your or if your pits or no?
Oh, yeah, I shaved my balls and my pits. I don't want anybody to see my orange
The next thing they're gonna see is my dick in their fucking mouth. That's what they're gonna get a shout-off
Who are you talking about? Who's are you referring to me?
Yeah, I'm talking to you. Oh, okay. Okay. I'll see us. I'll see us coming up now
I'm gonna talk to this gay guy
Don't you love me Joe?
What Alex, what do you want? I love you, but what do you fuck I want you to admit that you're singing in your party's
Essles trying to bring his pound on that's what I want
I'll take that for now
Okay
Oh
Oh, they pee or something like
Okay
Now now it's getting like just now it's getting like words like this disrespectful or is this like I'm like
You know just like don't discuss like some of the shit like that and then you just say
Oh, you got the unbuckling Marley Marlin would act like that Alex has been your friend for a long time
He's gonna attack you like that. That's fucked. I know. I know
This makes me wonder is like because it's like I
You should you should really know better
You should know you should know you can sit back stage you can sit back stage and we'll see see how long
I know I can be an asshole when I get drunk and talk, but at least you showed him who's boss is if he's gonna talk to you like
That he needs to be shown who the fuck the boss. Yeah, it's just a
First of all when when first of all when I talk Alex, you know, it's you know
It's like I mean other people yeah
You can like let people speak and like give one to one at a time
But if I'm saying something, you know, it's my show you're supposed to like at least pipe down a little bit
It's like, okay, not just like scream over me accusing me of
Being because who's the people that are trying to get my own mouth? It's offensive at some point. Okay. Stop it Alex
You like took too many of some kind of mushroom or something
I don't know. You're shipping out on but that's why I don't shirt with my teeth
I want to unbutton your buttons with my teeth on that shirt. That's all I want to say. Thank you
Well, you're sure there are your teeth aren't your teeth busy pulling
are your teeth are your teeth are your teeth busy pulling um
Bees out of 40 diamonds, but they're very busy. They're busy with jamie's cowboy. I'll watch them like right well
I want to watch that. I'm sorry. I can't I know
Okay, so hold on. No, no, no, don't talk about jamie's cowboys that way. Please
Okay, I apologize, but somebody put handcuffs in the chat. That is funny. Put your hands behind your back
You go to jam
One time I did go to jail and it was so cold and I got arrested with my boxers on no t-shirt
No pants, and it was so fucking cold. It was only like 20 hours
But it was the coldest 20 hours
And when I was in that cell I just said I wish Jamie's Cowboys was here
And they're like why why do you wish she was here?
I said, because I want to lick her from her head to her toes.
OK, OK, Alex, Alex, Alex, I don't have Jamie.
I don't have Jamie wants to have this conversation.
Jamie, Jamie, just tell them to stop.
Hey, hey, no, no, no, no, no, no, Jamie, just tell me.
I'll kick them off.
Um, yeah, I can't add it because it's like, I mean, I, I can bring you on the panel and then you can add it from the panel, but I can't, um, I can't bring on my, I don't have my computer running. I'm sorry.
Did you just tell somebody to kick me off? Like, oh, if you want to do it, just kick you off.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, she asked us to get, she wants to play a clip and I said she can play it, but she'd have to put it on through my stream yard. I can't add it myself because I don't have like a media share available.
I'm going to buy a nail brush. I'm going to I'm going to as soon as they get paid soon. I'm gonna get a nail brush, okay?
I mean what I'm thinking my list of it. I'm selling
Space bullion nail brush
If you really if you really care that much, you know, you can you can recommend one and maybe you'll put up my wish list
And maybe you can buy it for me
Then you can be responsible for cleaning my nails. Okay, so
Not talking about your nails. Look at my nails. They look at one time when I was like younger. They said Joe
You have Ninja Turtles. Hi. Hi. What's up? That's sexy beast. Oh
It's a cartoon. I'm pretty sure I want to fuck that robot. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay, Joe Joe
Hold on my AC's on let me let me turn it off. Hold on. Oh when you talk and talk say something right now, DJ
Let's just say hi
It's actually actually Alex you ever see Roger Rabbit. This is an actual living cartoon that it comes in
I have bigger tits than Jessica Rabbit to
Jessica Rabbit, yes, I remember that redheaded
No, when I was a kid they had the Nintendo game, we liked Roger Rabbit and that guy,
remember?
I remember.
It was like Roger Rabbit's handler, like, oh, I'm a fucking handler.
He was a detective that he's a detective that Roger hired because, you know, he's being
framed for his, something about his wife or something, right?
I don't know.
No, his wife hired him.
Roger Rabbit.
Roger got framed.
Yeah, Roger got framed.
Roger Rabbit.
I don't remember the whole story. He goes missing or something, and then Jessica Rabbit, but she's really framing him, right?
Something like that, yeah. I think she hires the detective because, yeah, he goes missing and then it's like, then it's like, but it was maybe...
I won't! I won't! I won't! I won't! I won't! I won't! I won't! I won't! I won't! I won't!
We're watching we're gonna watch a clip right now. Let's watch a clip
Remember this song?
Remember that?
What name that song?
DJ Electra
He asked me
Could you share with me?
Share with me?
That song
That was earlier tonight. That'd be considered fair use under the parody
Oh, please give us a copyright for Riley Martin.
This is AI though.
It's an AI song.
So you can try it.
I call it earlier.
Moist dad.
I'm moist dad.
You're very moist.
And a bye for now.
That's so cool.
This is the outside that I made.
Riley's dead into the starlit night
Wondering if they come back take him on a flight the cosmos health secrets are spoken
Life stands to cross the midnight sky
He hope they will show
To a world where words are the token
Riley when they you let it get hearts to do anything about it
It was great
So awesome, I didn't I didn't know anything about Riley. I didn't know anything about Eric when we started that one either
What happened to Joe?
I don't know
Yeah, Joey
Happy to meet all
I love it. I love it. I'm scared. I'm scared of Alex just kidding.
That's going to be Alex. Hi, Alex. Hey, Jamie's cowboy.
That was a very sweet way you said as long as you have it.
As long as you have a rabies shot, Alex, Alex is fine to be around.
But you know, it's like, don't I don't know.
I might need a tetanus shot to hang out around him also.
He does bite he does bite and he is yeah
He's this way right now. He thinks that everybody's everything. It's like, you know, we had that one
It's an understanding
Yeah, we mean you had that one thing with what's his fucking now. It's like everybody's everybody else now
He's apparently Michael like we see mom to and you know, he's every it gets it gets very complicated
It's very I'm very confused because I'm talking to people the same phone at the same time and
Some of them personally like you know more but it's like I don't know. Maybe it's a big conspiracy Alex
I better just go cry and the state for the state
I'm not pyre on up, but I might be a piranha
Now that's the sound that piranhas make underwater
Alex you're gonna come up and behave you can come up and say hi if you behave yourself, but
If you if you harass like the investigator for your channel. Yeah, he's your
Joe's man, but I was like, I was like Joe the PI will like, you know, not just like sentence the guy
I know it and like, you know, it'd be in charge of everything. It's like the yeah, I think
You don't freaking give away
Yeah, the information
Yeah, you told everything you know already. Yeah
What's our advantage now?
But now they can just now they can just all deny it and and change the name of the group to you know
to the mother kind of
I just love Raleigh Martin, I'm so glad somebody's saying no fuck that she wants.
Yeah, we do a whole show on him, it's fun, and we do Bigfoot, every other week we do Bigfoot and then Raleigh.
If you don't know who the fuck Robin Quivers is, Robin Ophelia Quivers.
We know who Robin is.
You better know who she is, she powers fat bone.
She was there for how we're when no shut up psyche when Howard was sad
Who is there for him Robin quivers?
Well, I know I'm a favorite. Okay. I'm a favorite story. I try to tell I think Gotti this is it
But he doesn't know or I think he didn't know who she was
But I was trying to tell this a story where it's like
I remember the Jesus was but let me tell the story real quick Alex
There's a story where like Howard like through a dinner for the staff and it was like it was really really expensive
New Yorker I don't remember the name of the restaurant. It's just one of those real expensive ones
you know probably like a couple hundred dollars a dish and
So he goes with that and he got he goes with like writing
You know he goes with you know Beth and then Robin
I don't know if Robin was dating but Robin was there and then a lot of the writers were there and you know Fred and
And so and already was there and Benji and Benji was there and so
Uh, so yeah, Benjy bronc. And so I don't think Alisa was there, but you know, I don't know if there were day, but so
So they go in the order and then and then Howard's like well Robin
Why don't you why don't you why don't you pick out the glass of the bottle of wine? And so Robin was like, okay?
Yeah, and so and so she or she or so she ordered
So she she the waiter talked her and she gave a bottle and he brought back the bottle and Howard is not in he poured the port it
And then, you know, halfway through dinner, the waiter comes back and he's like, would you like to continue with the wine?
And Howard's like, yeah, get another two bottles on there.
Would you like another bottle, man? Would you like another bottle?
He's like, yeah, two of them. And so then, you know, they come back with two bottles and then it's great wine.
Everyone enjoys it. And then, and then so they bring the bill.
there's like an envelope there and he opens the envelope and there's like the labels of the bottles
like a real special like you know like as a keepsake these and uh and then he looks at the bill and he goes
The wine was eight hundred dollars a bottle that okay. Yeah, the thing is also like
Robin order Robin order because because then the guys that you want to compete with the wine and he's like yeah
Like you know with her wine, but he didn't know it was eight hundred dollars a bottle
He thought it would be like a reasonable price cook out at her house and already got
I love he's like I do love you to death, and I love that robot. Where the fuck that fucking robot is
It's gonna avatars, okay, she's not called a robot. She's not like
Avatar
You're not
Yeah, we can what we can listen to fill my ubiquity
But he's too tired
Oh, wait, I think it's right
Okay, he's on sale at the I cracked the Liberty Bell
Joe dancing they do we some good dancing
Feel my ubiquity
Where's when they do? Oh, this is
Yeah, it's very jazz very jazzy song
Forgot I forgot
Yeah, we have a bunch of footage of him too. This is what I've been talking about
Okay, look at that ball, burn it up, burn it up, burn it up, burn it up, burn it up, burn it up, burn it up, burn it up, burn it up, burn it up, burn it up, burn it up, burn it up, burn it up, burn it up, burn it up, burn it up, burn it up, burn it up, burn it up, burn it up, burn it up, burn it up, burn it up, burn it up, burn it up, burn it up, burn it up, burn it up, burn it up, burn it up, burn it up, burn it up, burn it up, burn it up, burn it up, burn it up, burn it up, burn it up, burn it up, burn it up, burn it up, burn it up, burn it up, burn it up, burn it up, burn it up, burn it up, burn it up, burn it up, burn it up, burn it up, burn it up, burn it up,
It's so terrible, like, it's not terrible, okay, hold on, okay, come on, we gotta play the song,
I'm trying to get to the song. I mean, it is terrible, but in a good way. I mean, Howard,
like their look, I don't think the musicals are that great. Here's where they were in the...
Sucks like bush
Got this thing against bush too, which is hilarious. Yeah, that's true. That's weird. This is hair curls his hair curls
I don't like all these bands can be gone as soon as the Jesus twins don't help
Bush still planches while it's they suck
Everyone sucks the red hot chili peppers. They suck their professional
I agree with the Jesus twins a soundtrack go from one soundtrack to another right you're saying you're a fresh sound
That was exactly what they said the first
All these particular subjects.
Oh, here's Mendelssohn.
OK, here's more of their dancing.
My life, I would jump.
Oh, I love it.
And these guys are trying to make it clear.
That's all.
Yeah, I love it.
What's that? I said that really shook them. They're like quiet now and sitting down
For the show
How do they think this was good I'm gonna ask this question repeatedly because I don't get it
When they were making this video they were sitting there thinking
This is awesome.
There it is!
We're going to turn it up also!
Let it play. Let it play.
Hey, Ali!
Joe! Joe!
He's playing a recording of his show.
There you go.
Do you think what do I think I can't put it on the soundtrack why because it's already been pressed
Remember that they wanted it on the
Parts and it was probably it was probably not already pressed to
I think the songs were already approved for, but I don't think that CD was, I think I could have had the editors if they wanted to, but did anybody remember when Howard actually got a call from a guy that was going to jump off the bridge?
Who sang Howard's theme song, American Nightmare?
Who sang American Nightmare Howard's theme song, please?
Rob Zombie?
Who?
Rob Zombie!
Hell yeah, son.
It was Rob Zombie.
It was
Characters from his you know, yeah, he does all those horror movies
Yeah
Through the bitches and drag on a back of my drag you
I do love those songs like memory though one time DJ lecture being my brother used to laywares like feast on the cat
Remember the song by Rob Zombie where he says feast on the cat
I don't want to hear about eating cats, please
No, I don't want to hear
I just told you I don't want to hear about it. And then you then you every second people we need to learn like that
When you know, no, no, no, I see back stage. I see what you're crazy, right? No, no, no
I was telling you I was I don't say that anymore and then you said it
That's gonna be pretty why I said it as I just don't say that one thing you say that one thing like I said
It's like I'm almost up to like
Not tell anybody anything so they they like they'll I need to use reverse psychology because it actually doesn't work pretty well on a lot of people here
But I mean it's like you guys stop it. Stop it. So just stop it. Don't make me. Don't make me use my psychological tricks
I'm trying to be good
Psychological tricks
Yep, psyche is getting really
Psychology of trolls guys, that's why I have trolls behind me. Yeah
the
Joe, she cannot prove it on my show that big as to us
So it's a Memphis say you are in the book a lecture. I wrote your name down in the book
I'm just putting everyone's name down
Like spreadsheet for people from your chat
Look at nice book. You see the book. It says be kind
Yeah, I've had it for a couple years
Has my name on it has my name on it
What you wrote about us
You I mean, I didn't really write you just put your names down and stuff
One person that was famous. Who would you be? I
Will be John Lennon
Really, okay psyche, but the gentleman Joe. First of all, say Joe the name was assassins of Joe. So you want to be
That'd be like you say I want to be Abraham Lincoln. First of all, it's not the best thing in person in the world. Second of all, I don't want to meet his end. Okay. So, I don't know, Joe. I mean, Joe, you look like Abraham Lincoln.
You don't look like John Lennon. You don't look like John Lennon, but he was out of bed trying to come across my head.
Right. Well, it kind of reminds me a little bit of Fred Durst. I mean, I
Don't know. He seems to disappear from the chat tonight. I don't know. He fell. I think he fell off the panel
He was talking about it. He sounded like he was wearing a robe with like a
Way
I
Was looking at you
This is what we do here. This is this Joe. Let's see. This is what we like sing duets to each other and like our sweet
We don't we don't say horrible things about
Everything everything about each other. Okay, so let's we should be nice things. Okay, Joe. Do you hear?
You have a list I have a list of yep
Things that have gone down and people that have gone should go down and yeah, am I on the top of the list?
I never take people down, but I'm like, I'll just make a note of it in case it comes up again in the future
or something. Yes, you have to do that. You have to do the list. That's why I had to spy on this. Yeah
I'll give a little bit of misdirection where it's like you don't
Give all your theories. I mean, maybe they probably heard like I think you've had maybe some correct
But you've had so much bullshit that it's like oh
But bro, I'm correct 20% of the time, but when I hit I hate you understand
And in me, Alex, your microphone is too loud.
Your microphone is too loud.
You've got to turn him down, Sakey.
Do you know how to turn him down?
I'm going to.
Alex, your mic is way too loud.
That's the only thing I'm going to be able to do now.
Alex, I've asked you several times,
don't put it up all the way.
I'm not touching anything.
You guys are not going to be doing that.
Alex, put it on all the way.
I always have to address you.
Your ship will keep saying bullshit about hurting people and hurting people.
Let me worry about that. I mean you just worry about keeping the show safe and respecting the rules like why do you keep I keep telling you I've told you several times
I don't know why he doesn't listen. It's like
You have a major malfunction Alex
And Joe yours. This is bad. Okay, and you're on the shit list
You're both getting you're both getting a pedigree and inverted pentagram makes your name
Which is in the case that you might be sent by Satan to bother me your ball sack
Okay, well, I want to carve you right out of the chat tonight. Okay, so they're gone for the night. Okay, so I
Mean it's like I told me, you know, even if it's a funny joke. It's like it wasn't like, oh, that's it's not funny at all
It's just like all it is is just offensive, you know
Anybody, okay, so go away go away and Alex you can go away too tonight. I had enough. Okay had enough
Yeah, they left okay. Oh
They left a big mess in the green room. Oh, I don't know what you are. You got Stephanie Tanner
I mean go back to Full House Joe
The milk man the tape were on their way
Dr. Stan are we doing cards? Yeah, I'll do cards, but yeah, I prefer you come on panel Dr.
Stem or else I'll just pull a card for you in the chat
if you'd like one, but we can
Purchase a more detailed reading. I can do on the chat or panel
So
I'm proud of the 20% will gulana 20% hit rate. Whoa. What is this one?
You know, I get my my my like rate is like I get some of the like 2,000
People coming to my show throughout the night and I get that maybe about 30 likes 40 likes
So it's like hardly anybody likes my like nobody likes that. I'm always like, oh, well, I guess I don't like my show
like knowing and I sometimes I say like and remind them but
That doesn't really matter though. The like how many people like that that number really doesn't matter
The numbers that you want to look at are in analytics in I mean this might be boring
Tell me to shut up if it's driving you nuts, but in the YouTube studio under analytics go to your click-through rate
I think it's called click-through rate or your shit. What's it called? No, I think they changed the name
Yeah, I I think I have seen it and it's like yeah, it's like there are
Engagement engage me. Yeah, it's like the viewer engagement which is but it's like this only but it does help with it
When you do the light your impressions
If you I guess it I suppose it even helps if you hit the dislike it probably even helps because that's like some kind of engagement
That's true, but I mean and it's good. Please everyone
please like it every little bit helps right we've got to do everything I'm just
seeing if if you want you know what you should do sometimes you should go
straight live on YouTube on a vertical phone don't go through StreamYard like
it so you know when you go on your walks
Like here and stuff. Yeah, you should go vertical and just go straight through stream yard
Because that's okay. I can't their live algorithm
I can't even have a panel like on the period more because it's like people are just trying to do too many things and
You just got to do sometimes do one of those solo streams
Like you know, I'm walking around LA for three hours yesterday and people were watching good
Do you know do you know rogue nomads tonight showed a firearm on the on the show and said he was gonna
Um, it's whatever he should fire arm and then alex alex was telling
People to unalive themselves and and wrote and wrote no my was like
It's like and it's like as I get heavy in the stream and it's like because it's like even the mod I had mods in the chat
They're like, oh that they're like that's like it's like it's gone too far
And it's like because it you know how far it goes and it's like but it's like it's getting to the point
And I keep telling them stop and they're not stopping and so it feels like it's like malicious at this point where they can't even
You know, that's like it's like I understand some people are not able to be reigned in
But it's like to be just like militia. It's just like it seems like a malicious thing where it's never kidding that they're not
Understand
It's like it's like they have to be like honestly
They have to be like when do the retard was to have the 20 IQ points on them? Okay, or when do that slow adult?
She does. Yeah, she must I mean you think it's like she's our panel. Yeah, like she used to put her link in chat
We finally got her to stop doing that because she was getting porn bombed every night
by this guy named Joe Walsh. Not the real Joe Walsh, like that's in the Eagles, but the frickin, some porn bummer.
And he would come on there every night, and American Dream was up there with his brown star fish showing and stuff.
It was just all bad, and so we're like, Wendy, you gotta stop putting your link in chat, only go send it to people that you know on Discord, that you actually want on your show.
And so that was one change that she made that helped.
I don't know, maybe at some point you might want to do that.
Because you know-
I mean, I'm about almost to the point where I'm like,
maybe I'll just put the link on the Discord.
But then the Discord people have the same,
the kind of the same people there too.
Yeah, but you can do that privately to them
in the message, in Discord.
It's just a lot, it's a lot, it's a lot.
It's like, they're running the show and like, you know,
sending PM, I mean, it's like, I can do it.
it's worth it or you can have you know me I can help or you know stuff you can ask people to help you if you're
overwhelmed. Yeah. Um, that's just a thought. I mean, it really helped her. She never ever got any other streams that she had to take down after that. I shouldn't be overwhelmed, but it's like, it's not, it's not that I'm overwhelmed at all. It's like that I'm purposely, it's like they're, it's like I'm purposely being attacked in order to like get, get, get reaction or to get, get them attention. Yeah. And then say, and I understand, and it's like, and it's like, oh my God, it's, and it's like it once.
It's like it's like I thought like you know what I had like my channel is like
Is you know me I couldn't go on the two pans for a few days?
And no, like you know people that come to my show and my my panel did fine elsewhere, but
There's often a cucumber up his ass on my god show
And put a freaking vegetable
In orifice, I just wrong that is just one Wendy is a virgin
Yeah, you know like come on people. Oh, yeah, that was so like not cool. I wasn't here for that. Thank God
I don't know
I don't know if you were here, but when like I had this person illy on the show and he's like, you know
This is Vladimir Putin's like
Assistant or something and he has like a he has like this it looks like a resuscitation and resuscitation Annie or CPR Annie
We go yeah
Then he and then he's normal and then he like and then he all of a sudden like turned around
I'm sort of pulling down his pant
I just ended the stream
but who knows how far he would have gone with it and then I like and then I had him back on the panel and
Then he's like well
Can I be the first person in your stream to piss in a bucket and I was like no you may not I was like as like you know
You just pee in the bathroom
I don't want to and then then as they and then I was like oh I'm gonna go with some fish tacos
And I was like looking at the menu the restaurant all of a sudden I hear a peeing sound
and then uh and I was like I was like what are you and then he's like sitting there and then
Everyone's like oh, he just poor mom. Do you he showed his penis?
He pan the camera down onto his small penis. Yeah
And I had talked and so it's like it's just fun. It's just explaining to them and so it's like I
I can't even let him know it bothers me because then it's like though. Oh, that's it's funny
Just to bother me right because it people don't like me. So it doesn't bother me guys
Alex and I'll be on fat in chat
Yeah, I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I
Yeah, you can't you can't you remind me of Scarface where you just had he has like his basically he has a desk in front of him
It's just a mountain of cocaine a mountain a mountain of it and he has there's some poor woman in there
I think it's his wife or something like that. She just hides away and
Then he just yells at her and throws straws at her, you know, and sometimes sometimes stacks of money, but and then
Then the police can you target someone that is not trying to help psyche?
Can you target someone that is actually trying to harm him?
Yeah, Alex target me you were so not productive like that's so ridiculous
I just don't understand you. I know and Alex I I met them different places. I mean, it's like they're just completely
It's like I know I I know it's like unless you're destroying Alex. It's like
Really that I was reading yesterday. There's some kind of mental disorder where it's like people see doubles
They see like they see then you know, sometimes people make connections
But it's like these people will see it like really so strongly that they'll think ever the doppelganger
They'll think someone they've known for 20 years the replacement
Yeah, there's another word. What's you remember the word?
It's not pie. Is this but it doesn't matter. I try to explain it. He just he won't like
And so it's like maybe maybe it's just better if you just stay in the chat Alex cuz it's like I need to talk to somebody with like some kind of
You know at least a little bit of rash like anything. I can't be talking to like you're like sweating because you've been talking to these people for hours
Oh my god. Oh my god, Alexa. Alexa. My hair is falling out. My beers are completely white. My skin is terrible now
I'm like not sleeping. I'm not eating. I'm eating terrible levels are too high. You're
Is just going on stop. Oh, I can be hard. I can be harvest for that
that Hollywood, Hollywood chemical, you know, and, you know, feed a large Mormon family or
something. But I don't want that to happen. Electra has her, yes, Electra's, Electra's
completely, I mean, it's like, you know, sometimes I flip out, you know, I went on a channel
a while back and like a couple weeks ago and like screamed at the top of my lungs and they
clipped it. They did a show on me, Psyche, for two hours. They covered me.
and what I said on a show where they were basically
ganging up on me.
Anyway, it doesn't matter.
I don't care.
But it's just hilarious that like,
people.
I remember the first time I got,
I got, the first time I, I mean,
I got clipped for like little things on my show,
but I remember the first time like,
I saw like a whole show made out of me
was Carolus Kate and she had named the show,
Psyche.
Because I had
She just your headphones clipped out. Oh, yeah, I want it
Do you hear me? Okay. So it was called psyche. It was called psyche the weirder lurker because
There's like I was being I was being poor mom and then I was on I was on her discord to keep an eye on things
And then I would see the discord message to pop up on my phone
Ever after I got poor mom saying oh, yeah poor Bob are like with the pictures of it and everything
I was like, well, that's weird. Like they know exactly why I got poor mom
I guess you know, it is the thing she does was the document porn bombs and stuff like that
but I was just like I just had the question and
and so
Yeah, um, do you ever you know, I don't know ever heard that saying we're like people
That don't have any original thoughts. Just talk about other what other people do, right?
Because that's my you're a very interesting person and you have a lot to say so people that don't have much to say tend to
Want to say the most wait. Yeah, they want to know what you're doing because you're interesting
That's why sometimes I can I can be quiet and it's like people women know I can leave the panel
It's sometimes they notice but most of the time they don't there's like I'll do it when they're just talking all
Notice when you leave psyche we always notice everybody does you might not always say it
I usually am like, where'd it take you go?
But yeah, we noticed, don't worry.
But some of that time, I'm not even like,
there's like Alex screaming,
I'm people are not even able to talk for like the last
and a half hour and so I was like,
oh yeah, but I was like,
so much difference is that they're still screaming at people.
You gotta turn his mic down almost to off.
He's gonna because he yells first of all second of all I was Mike is up to a hundred percent
I was doing that one night, and it's like it was so funny because he was screaming
But then it's like you hear me clearly and everyone
You hear like a little little little mouse in the back screaming in the back
Our secrets out yeah
It's okay. It's okay. So so you know JJ JJ wants to say hi to you
JJ
Or he left okay. Oh
Yeah, that's JJ. He's he's a cool guy. He's actually he's out. He's yeah
He's actually mini Manson that he gave you the only one mini Manson would let up on my panel
Oh, here's on the other night. He was like me man. I'm like
More at blues. Yeah
Yeah, yeah, I actually made a clip of Minnie Manson. I believe seeing that. Yeah, I think yeah
Did you see the art card lecture and also did you know?
Minnie Manson was on the show the other night
And we made up and everything. Oh, that was cool. I'm glad. I'm glad. I like mini you stringer ballet or JJ. Is that your name?
I'm sorry
Okay, so you're Bella's a character from a wire. Okay, so you know but your friends with mini-man sent you
I'm a fan. I'm a mini-man some fan. Nice. I had him on my show back like a year and a half ago
Maybe almost two years ago
Like it was like one of my first episodes of the show that I started doing
Interesting. Yeah
My co-host totally was misgendering him. It was like
Oh boy get your frickin pronouns, right? Oh my god. Mini was really cool about it though. He was like, it's all right
We're gonna work through this
You know
He's so old. He's like yeah, he's very old. The one thing about mini is that not mini
Mini mini mini has this tendency that if he hangs around someone too long he ends up turning on them
Yeah, I felt that I felt that before
Well, you know what that you know, you know what that happens you know what that happens sometimes
It's a in narcissism. There's something called the mask that people were and it's like so this is like
I was like when people have a YouTube, you know, it's just like I
My channel, this is a persona because I you know, I have the ability to
Present to you what I want to present and anybody that comes here presents themselves as they want to be present themselves
And so it's hard to decipher what's real. I was not but the mask if you do if you do or I really don't wear a mask
I'm very much myself and you can tell cuz I'm just pretty much the same person
But the mask on narcissists who are can be malignant the woman most people are a little bit narcissists
But the more malignant ones that are actively try to hurt other people or to humans animals that kind of stuff
The mask it's a hard to maintain a mask for a very for a long time
It evidently will it will slip and then the real they did have and then they did then then what happens
It's called doopers to light where they'll slip and they'll say oh they didn't notice
Guys notice it when it does we know then yeah, do you notice and then give them a doopers to like smile back
Give them give them one back and they'll freak out. Yeah, but I think what Minnie Manson does is
Many if you're here, I would tell you this too. I think that he actually
Kind of goes after people a little bit after he knows him for a while and kind of test them
It's like I think it's a test. It's like to see how you will react to his kind of a little bit of a
Freak out not really a freak out
But just a little bit of a glitch in the matrix if you want to call it that I don't know what else to call it
But you're right and I get it. It's like a test and we all you know
Have different ways that we vet people and different ways that we build trust with people
Oh, yeah, and I think that might be a way to see like how do you react?
Are you gonna completely turn on him or are you gonna you know be?
patient and accepting and want him back in your life.
But were you there?
Were you there?
Yeah, you're right.
But were you there the other night
when we had the little altercations?
Like did you see that episode or no?
I missed the altercation part.
I saw part of that episode, but I was working,
but I was in and out, so I didn't see the altercation.
So Minnie and I were like in contact.
Like Minnie's like, I want to come on the show.
Like, but then I get, but Minnie's said,
hey, but Minnie's like,
oh, I just want to be the only one on the panel.
And so I was like, sure.
Okay.
And then,
I kind of like, you know, I was kind of drunk and I kind of forgot and then it's like also I saw some oh
Hey, I think God the guy guy it was God in the check
I was like a God he is a mini I think mini fan because he had been on the episode before talking to mini mini life
So I brought me a I brought him up and then mini like
Got very upset. I've got very mad that I
wrote the thick with the agreement and it's like which is my which is my fault and
but
Mini me started writing me saying
You, you hate me, you think I'm a, you call me a little cow behind my back and you laugh
at me, you're getting people to laugh at me and you think my name is Naomi.
And I don't know. I think your name is new. Yeah, but I don't think that I don't think that mini is a narcissist
I really don't know. I wasn't referring to really mini when I was talking about that. I was
Oh, yeah, well
HK Memphis shade don't take any of them. She says too seriously. Well, she's the she's the she's the managing mod here
What are you talking about?
What's wrong with Shay? She's a very, very kind person.
Don't, don't trust, you know, girls in the streets. That's all I gotta say.
Hey, hey, are you a girl from the streets? What's that mean?
Um, she, she is a lady of the night.
an escort. It's an escort. It's the oldest profession in the industry of the world. Yes, she's an escort.
An escort. You know, an escort keeps somebody company, a lonely person company, and it's a business
company. I don't see anything wrong. An escort. I don't think there's anything wrong with it either.
I mean, also, I think someone was asking, oh, someone said, oh, Floory, how much for a blow job
or something? And Floory's like, Floory said, I don't charge for it.
Sexual act I charge for the the time we spend together. It's like the time. It's not so it's like oh my god
It's a technicality, but it's a very smart thing. It's true. Hey flirty diamonds for their time
um people
Are paying for the diamond. I promise you and you know, oh, you're
She's saying that you're thinking of somebody else. Maybe. Oh, I'm thinking filthy filthy. Huh, filthy. What do you think?
No, I'm a little bit confused.
I don't understand why a man would pay for sex
with a woman that has a penis versus sex with a woman who doesn't.
Have you heard of Jim Norton?
A fetish?
Yeah, have you heard of Jim Norton?
You know some guys like a big dick on a ship?
Are you talking about like Fight Club Jim Norton?
They like the female image, but then like under the underwear and stuff,
they like the other.
parts and that's it's it's it's like a fetish it's like everybody so they're closet no because
they like the femininity part of it they were attracted to a female and so it's it's it's
femininity of their penis no no it's um i can't explain it i'm not that way but i don't know
Sex with a guy with a dick
The training training chasers and it's like people that you could think are straight straight men or just like normal men
That are very attracted to the transsexual part
Who knows why but it's like and some people are just attracted to different things
But there are a lot of trans women that are
Absolutely gorgeous. Yeah. Yeah. Gorgeous. Yes. They are so passable and they are beautiful
Especially nowadays
Well, I I know but I think
It's very pretty though. I think it's very pretty.
Florida isn't very attractive person. Florida isn't
Florida isn't
Oh, maybe maybe maybe say you're tight, but you know, I was like, I like my I like Mexican guys personally
I'm on time in Florida, but I was like, I like I like tattooed Mexican gangster guys and it's like that's very weird and people wouldn't think I
I'm sorry
Oh come on
Come on, you're just being mean now
Yeah
Yeah, and for them it's not coming over demanding a date or money or anything like that people go to flurry diamond
You know and so it's like
Oh, come on
Well, I mean, yeah, I mean
Confronting psych about that
But I do I do have one point. I hope for diamonds listen
I do have one point to say 30 diamond
It is very very very dangerous to be out in the streets as a trans person
And it's like there's people like you confuse those people especially in Los Angeles or it's very dangerous
live streams. Yeah, that's what I'm saying. I'm saying, can you just do the live streams? Can you
just go on the internet and then you're not near people and you can like have a kind of safety
like that way but it's like just don't go down the blade. You don't want her to do live streams
on the stream? No, no, I don't want her to do just the prostitution. She's just the...
Well, we don't know that she's... No, she said she said she said that she's live streamed herself
No, I'm saying no, she has she missed it and it's like but I'm saying literally live from fig
On fig on the street
Yeah, but I'm gonna say flurry diamond. It's better to especially now with the internet and it's like you can you can work the internet to like
Bring even better than on the streets and it's not it's not this dangerous
That's all I'm worried about the dangerous because there's people that will freak out about
If they if they because you are very passable and so
And so people will people look can get fooled, right? If you when you're patented this part of the
So it's like it's a big thing. I just want to I just want you to be safe for you. That's all I mean, okay?
So no no shade. No shade
I mean, did you do you do what you want to do your life?
But I do worry about you like, you know late at night
Los Angeles is just not a
Not a not a place for a nice that nice nice lady. You just sit a computer and maybe book dates from that like in a
That's probably yeah, just I mean there there's a record there's an electronic record of all the communications and stuff is a safer
And there's a lot of platforms to do that on now
For sure. Yeah, there's a lot of forms that people are making bang
What sound pussy like only fans or chatter bait or whatever these
Well, you're right it's next work, but it's like
You know, it's selling selling media and it's like and there's also so much media out there
It's like doctor and I'm in real and so it's like no one even knows the looking at anymore when look at media
But at least it's like I've seen these chatterbait girls and they these guys
I know that have open panels or whatever they'll have these chatterbait girls come on
These girls have a loop of a 10-second video
That is pre-recorded maybe 15 seconds and it just loops over and over again, and they're not even talking
They're not answering questions there. They'll come on maybe because they're on another channel talking to someone that's paying them
Yeah, they're advertising on this free panel, and then they're over here doing whatever God knows what but they have like this looped video running
It's just it blows my mind. I would never freakin do that a lecture. I've heard of Pete. I heard of somebody making
I think it was like a hundred grand, but it might be more like a hundred grand a month
Just having AI generated porn on the only fans and then they did have it
Have an AI character just generate the poor and they all for free and then it's like it's like, you know
Pretty crazy guys. If I could take my clothes off as this character. I probably would
Well, I mean but it every time I try to take my clothes off as this it like put the black shirt over me
Like yeah, I think I tried to wear a bathing suit once because we were on jet skis in one of the shows and uh
It's like a bathing suit. Yeah, I just put like a frickin rash black rash guard on me
Wet suit, yeah
Like a three three inch wet suit 30 wet suit. It was like the hoodie and the booties and the
Well, did you ever watch 90 a fiancee? Yeah, so there's a season and the guy's name is
I don't really watch reality TV show, but I did see I've seen a couple because my old roommate did
Well, there's a woman named Nicole Nicole's like a she's like this really cute like kind of airy-fairy kind of blonde
Fashion, I think she's a fashion designer. She's in LA and real pretty. She's also like, you know, real like a model
She's like looks great in all the outfits. It's a really cute style. So she met this guy from Morocco. His name is ma mood
And, you know, he's and so they met and like she already had moved back home because it was like she she moved with him and his whole family and
The old woman little apartment and it was and it was just overwhelming and they're having a comfort to Islam and stuff
Oh, sorry to interrupt. Can I just mention that my friend Char Batty is in chat? Oh
Just saw your comment. She said do you charge for reading psyche? I will do free reading in another chat room
Oh, yeah, I'll do a free reading for you
If you want to go on panel or in the chat, I'll do a free reading if you want like a more detailed reading
You know a small donation
If you're still here come on up panel or if you just want it from chat, but so you were
Talking about 90 day. Yeah 90 fiance. So so there's this couple and they were like fighting a lot
But you know because she was like this. She's also like this very like, you know
Dresses kind of sexy. She was you know dresses like and then he's very like, you know
They some rock and see he kind of they even have at the coffee shops there
They're women aren't even allowed there and she would want to go to the coffee shop and then like everyone
We're looking at her like why is she here like it's like it would just be such a such a
Culture clash, but the funny thing was like there's like let's go to a pool today and she's and he's like, okay
I picked you out of outfits aware, you know
Uh-huh. He basically goes out to the pool in a speedo or like it's a baby
No, he's in a bathing suit. You know, it's like a she comes out. It it looks like like lost in space like the alien
It's like she it's a it's called the burkini. It's like a full wetsuit with with the headpiece like a look at Oompa Loompa like wrapped around
And she comes down. She looks so sad in it. They got a big fight. You might want to check out the that season
Let's see. You wish to watch. Yeah, it's really funny. I
kind of want to wear those now like I I think I have like a skin cancer spot on my back psyche
I'm really nervous I have to go to the doctor because it's like this little spot and you know
I grew up in Southern California and I was getting some burns like all the time we were not good
about sunscreen you know well I have a lot of moles in my back and if I always have my moles
checked and I think they're always you get them checked yeah I need I never had it checked it's
It's just been there. Well, I mean they I mean those those the dermatologists will just just have a look at it and it's
Very I think it's the most one of those deadly forms of cancer
And so you do want to have it there because all they do is look at those. I mean, I heard it is it's melanoma
Can be yeah, yeah
Now my friend. Yeah, he was fine and then one day
He started getting these stomach aches and like really bad. He thought he had IBS or something and
They did a colonoscopy. He had melanoma
in his colon
Yeah, not on his skin. Yeah, I mean it's spreading and spreading and spread through that. Yeah
I mean the skin is larger so we're getting your body and you know, right and it can spread and so but he's been on treatment for over
Ten years now. He got on some trials and like all this stuff. I don't want to talk about cancer. Sorry, nurse me
I talk about some stupid shit sometimes. I hear you
J-Doc had a scare with a line on his toenail
a line you have a scared line of what is I know I mean any like little thing
that's off about us like we're like what's this and it's like you know
that's why you know a lot a lot of times they go have a lump and it will be
what's called like not malignant means bad what does it mean when it's when it's
when it's not active it's called something else in remission and it's
It's not it's not pieces on cancer. It's like there's something that people maybe they might might be they test it
And it's like it's not I don't know what the I don't know. Okay. Um
It's been not it's been nine been nine been nine. Thank you. It's a benign to me. Yes. God go go Bader. That's what you mean
Yeah, I'm sorry I wasn't
No, I'm not I'm not I'm not a hundred percent like you were dropping good at them good at the medical stuff either
I just he said yeah people would freak out your toenail from the sign of cancer
Well, yeah, because there are the things they oh this might be a sign of this, but there is a show called
Hey, we have another guest hold on one second. We have another guest. I mean, this is charlie or shark shark, baby
Okay, hold on here you go
Hello, hi
Okay, how are you tonight? I'm hanging in there. How are you doing DJ Electra? Good. I've missed you. How have you been?
Hey crazy kind of like, you know
On I don't know
Somebody had mentioned you in one of their panels or something. None of our friends
And it wasn't anything bad or anything, but I was like, oh, I've been wondering about you. So it's good to talk to you
Thank you. It's good to see you too. Yeah, I met you on a panel with Electra. I believe you came on Beast Modes.
I remember that's when I first met Electra. I remember I was doing readings in the chat.
I don't know if I gave Electra a reading the first time, but I do remember Electra.
Yeah, you did love it. It was really nice of you.
Yeah, I hear Alexander's back. Alexander, did you behave to Electra? Alex?
Like you know, you have a thing that says this is an example. Hold on. I want to hear about
You got your lumps
Like big little lumps like where like what do you mean lumps?
Lumps, you know you on your back. I have moles like you got on your back
I'm more like a hump. What do you mean? Yeah, I have two big humps. They're full of they're not full of them
So you're basically dying
I'll be gone any day, but you can just drink drink those. Yeah. Yeah
First thing that's the first more thing ever. Did you say I'll be gone any day because you can get to walking your doggy
No, it's true
He's a bit
Manic these days
He's a cool guy though. We like him. Yeah, I'm not that cool
Okay. Well, Alex has this, Alex has this thing where he thinks like everybody is everybody else, maybe sometimes he thinks that, you know, like people.
Yeah, he thinks people are alts.
I want to get up by your cancel arms, you losers. You know what cancel?
No, I don't want to hear it. Alex, that's really inappropriate. It's not the place for discussion. Okay, you know, we already said it's like a little bit too controversial even to bring up the name of it.
But then he's talking about that, Alex, and that's really inappropriate dealing with survivors.
No, Alex, you coming up for a reading. Did you want a reading? Yeah. Okay. I have a specific reason, but I didn't know if he needs
me to tell him that or what? Okay. Well, you can like you can tell me if you want or you just or you can just ask it very
generally or just say general. And I mean, I'm basically going to pull you a number and then or you give me a number
I'll pull you a card with that number. I'll pull you an extra card. Look at those two cards together and give you my
interpretation of the of the card designer. Okay. Thank you. I appreciate that. But he
can do more in-depth readings too if you ever want. Yeah. I have his info on discord too if you ever
okay. Yeah. So do you have a number between one and ten? Three. Okay three. Okay I'll
And I'll pull a car another car for you
Got this one for you, okay
Let's see what comes up
This is from the villains deck. This is a Disney deck. It's really cool. Okay. Okay, so you got this five of wands
Okay, so this
This five of wands is you know the poison apple, you know, and so it's like so it's competition
You know, it's like you know that the Queen was always competing in Snow White and there's jealousy there
And so, you know, there may be somebody jealous of you. That's
Are you trying to give you a poison apple or maybe some kind of
You know something in disguise because the apple and the apple was actually half with poison and half
half not with poison and so the evil Queen knew what to eat
But I'll tell you out of the book. So it says the five of wands
So it says
It says there is a conflict within a collaboration in your life and it's causing you
Just chaos believing
Blaming others won't make things go long. Blaming things often won't move
things using control your frustration and and then get the
Same communication. Okay. I'm sorry. I kind of got that guy that wrong, but it's like yeah
So this is basically it can be a competition. It can be a friendly competition. It can be
It's not as serious as the swords, but it's still there's a lot of passion involved in that
I mean your other car is gonna be okay the nine of points. Okay, so this is
This is like okay protecting what you have already. Okay, okay this with that. Okay, so maybe I
Think somebody might
Be at like that's what you will you have or jealous of it or something and you and you and you but you're
You're a button you had this abundant garden
So it's like you really need to protect it and you got to watch out for anything in the garden
You know just be careful to keep weeding it keep like looking for anything strange in it
And it's like this know that there might be some you know some
Garden the metaphor of course for your life in your world and so just you know keep an eye out because there might be like
I'm just seeing that I'm seeing a picture of a snake right now with with the apple, right?
I'm like some kind of
Some kind of maybe either a temptation or it's just like some kind of maliciousness
Maybe out of jealousy and so just watch out for the trickster energy. I'll put you an animal card real quick and this will be
To wrap it up
Your animal card is gonna be oh you got the butterfly
Butterfly means transformation, joy, lightness, and rebirth.
The metamorphosis of caterpillar and butterflies embodies the principle of physical and spiritual
transformation and the butterfly lighting upon a flower is the very essence of joy.
beauty and freedom. The butterfly has been symbolic of the soul, early Christianity,
conjugal bliss in China, and change and joy in Native America. In early Minoan
and Messinian cultures, the butterfly guides was a key emblem symbolizing a
new life after death.
In this painting, the woman's face is emerging from the chrysalis-like womb suggests transformation of a rebirth.
The anger-face of the butterfly has become to resemble a Christian Madonna or the Yehoan.
The upper-face of the butterfly
symbolizes the Christian Madonna, which reinforces the idea of a spiritual birth and a new life.
So it kind of looks like a Madonna there, a Virgin Mary.
Can you see it now?
Yeah.
And you know the word, you know the name Psyche actually means butterfly or soul in Greek.
And so that's where the name Psyche came from.
It's also a Greek goddess named Psyche.
So and she symbolized with butterfly wings often. So I hope you like that reading. I hope that
made some sense. And it's like you just want to I really get that idea of like they're like you
have this beautiful garden and it's like everything is flourishing and growing. And then there's like
a little like a little snake in the tree when it was like a little apple to offer you and say you
can eat this apple too. And this is funny. It's always like, you know, just always be aware. Always
You're birds flying up your finger like you're snow white and stuff like that, but you know not all the animals are friendly. Okay, right?
Okay, that makes a lot of sense. Thank you. You're so funny and you are so joyful and
You have like I don't know you just have this great energy about you
Thank you, and I don't want I don't know what's going on. I haven't talked to you in a while
Contact me anytime by the way. I miss you, but you know, don't let people take it from you
I'm trying. I
Am trying because I know you've been through a lot. Yeah online
Does he have a cash app or what does he do?
Yeah, I do it's just like you wait. It's like a dollar second sticky awakens anything is appreciated, but
You know and of course if you want more, you know, I'm always I'm always available to
pull cards and send her your um your discord and invite her to your discord?
absolutely are you still on discord char? no i i'm not i i got off of that but i
i i can join one that's not a problem i just stay on there just to keep in touch with people so
yeah i don't go on um like yeah i've kind of like my discord kind of went south a little bit and i
This is like a lot of it's like I like it because it kind of like takes some of the drama from the show and like you
Put on discord and safe on discord, but it's like the same time. It's like I kind of get
Kind of what I like he came on here to do tarot and cats and
He ended up getting like the gnarliest trolls
Oh, no, that's not cool. Yeah, you were so nice when when you came on beast mode
I just felt like you were genuine when you came on there
But um, and I like the fact that you like cats. That's that's a major
That's a major thumbs up. There's so many people in my chat
I love cats like so many people have cats and also. Yeah, and also, you know, I also expected like, you know
I'm a big fan of Howard Stern and
So I saw like I saw like the supreme like they call they called it goofy on people, but
Trolling is to get to a new level of goofy on people, right? Oh, yeah, on YouTube that's taken to a whole new level
Oh, yeah, I went real life with me, so I understand
Yeah, that was kind of good training done shows together or come on. We did one or two, right? Yeah, we did too
Yeah, and then we've been on many panels. We used to play poker together
Yeah, like almost every night you still play poker at all
a couple times a week, but it's getting to the point where I'll probably go back to my channel
But don't send me the links when you're going live because I don't know okay notifications, but I would love to come play
I haven't been playing at all. I have just been
Had to get a new computer and disaster happened like I had to get another new computer and it just been
technology
Issues and in trying to keep my shows
Going so I would love to complain
I need a break sometimes from oh, yeah, I hear you
Yeah, I heard very much upgrade. Oh, yeah, here we go. Yeah, that causes technological issues true
Starts with a D
Denizem Denizem. Hi Denizem. Hello
How are you? I'm very well. How are you? I saw you on Glenn Lawrence's panel last night. We're yesterday
Oh
Did I make a good impression? I
didn't kitty fruit. I didn't stay for long because I
Yeah, yeah, I just the whole red pill community just it bums me out really
How so just that men are blaming women and women are blaming men it's like hey
Dennis and remember me can't blame a whole no gender you do you know you do
remember me motherfucker if you're the real Dennis and you'll remember me from
TVP
This is not the real denizen. Please turn him down. Please. Shut the fuck up, bitch
No
Uh psyche, I was just gonna mention to you real quick before I jump back down you mentioned Howard Stern
Yeah, in the 80s. He was at my local radio station and went to my sister's
Prom with one of the girls. This is before he hit it big time. He see 101 is where he was at. Oh
My god
Yep, that is very cool. It was
He met him. Oh, yes. Yeah, he
Showed up at the whole school and that was one of the major radio stations back then it was right inside a
Maryland right outside of DC
Wow
Yeah, it was like oh, yeah, you know 84
Robin was I'm ago Robin was from Baltimore. Yeah, yep. She was there. Yep
Later on replaced by a guy called grease man and
He was went all I think California at one point, but he was crazy too, but yeah
They used to call him a shock jock
It's so funny because
Yeah
I haven't seen him in years, but
He was very funny like I
Mean these is corn ribs. They're like pieces of corn with like they're really good. They're from the pier like
I'll see you one here
They put barbecue sauce on him. It's like seasoning and like it's Tahin
The Mexican he put himself off. He he went away. He probably
Okay, corn, okay
Wow never seen that before it's really good
Yeah, so
Thank you for the reading. Yeah, you're welcome. Um, and I will be in touch with you, uh,
DJ.
Awesome.
Sorry, I just tried to send you a message and it wouldn't go through because we don't
share a server. Um, so, uh, in the back chat, you want me to just drop my, uh, email
Oh, yeah, I have a public email that I give out so I'll put it in private chat. How's that? Okay? That sounds great
That would be great. Thank you. Electra. Yeah, okay. Good. I'll write it down. Okay. Awesome
Look in the 80s how is children like relentlessly there we go
Make fun of like Kathy Lee and like Rosie O'Donnell
He's not like Alex talks to like people. Oh, Rosie O'Donnell the fat pig
Yeah, he leaves her and then um
You know and everyone kind of like would laugh and it was funny
Years later when Howard's buying a house in the Hamptons and then he's like he moves right next to Rosie O'Donnell and
Catty leaves across the street and it's like okay. It's like a little bit
So he made peace with them and I think now he's like all his testosterone went away like as men age their testosterone levels go out
the freaking window and they lose they get low T and I think maybe Howard did and
he was like well I don't have energy for this anymore I'm just gonna I do I do
think I do think he wears a wig I mean I don't think his hair could not be that
no not perfect I mean not after all these years no no I don't believe it
either no it would be thinner and gray
Yeah, at least at least at least if you're gonna wear the wig to get a fucking gray one or something
Make it a little more believable salt and pepper or something don't just like I have this perfect black hair still
I mean my beer has gray in it now and I'm 44 when that my beer is like tana claws have oh
Your beard wasn't up gray. I saw it the other day. You finally shaved. You were looking like a little bit like a homeless Bob
It was good talking to you guys. Thank you so much. You're gonna take night. Thank you. Bye. Bye. Bye back again. Yeah, I
Like her so much
She is so good at poker too. I
Mean I have my moments where I can kick ass, but she
Like routinely kicks ass a poker. Mm-hmm, you know
I'm still pretty new at it
So yeah, I haven't played in a while. I was telling Gaudi last night like
Remember to get a plain poker, but I am pretty good at the bluffing and the tells
Which is a big part of the poker. That's the hard part of doing it online is that it's hard to see people's tells
And if they're quiet and they're not or sometimes poker players yap a lot
And then it's hard online to to get those tells but the way you get the tells online is by their bets
So you have to watch how much they bet when they bet what you know after the turn the river whatever
When they bet and how much they bet and those are the the main tells online
Yeah, there's still things to analyze guys. You have to know what to analyze the drink is, you know, I'm sure it's a lot easier
It's up or playing in poker in person
It's like if you know anything about your language a lot easier, so yeah
I've never I so I learned how to play poker in during COVID. I'd never played and then I
So I've never actually played an in-person tournament
So I wonder if I would give a lot of tells or not or
Because I'm pretty good at keeping my hands like still, you know
like and not
I mean, I worked as a nurse and you're you're really in the public eye a lot and so
You have to really control your facial expressions
Because you could be looking at someone that has something really gross going on and you cannot you can't make a face
you know
Well, it's like really like
Like learning how to
Love is part of that and it's like you know and it's like because there's things on micro expressions and it's like people cannot help
when they, when you look at the cards,
you'll have your standard bluff face on.
There's going to be like a little centimeter
of someplace in your face that will move up.
It's a really good or a really bad card.
Right.
Or I might eat my eyebrow or something.
You know, like I get an itchy eyebrow
if I'm going to like losing it.
I don't know.
And that's why there's false tells.
I mean, it's like, so it has to be, you know,
it's like, you know, it's like-
Yeah, you can make false tells too.
So, I'm going to give you the option and you and Dan is, so I was in his back, Mr.
Black State, I think he was just rude and I don't know, I don't think he can control
himself tonight.
What do you think?
I think, I like Alex and I think if you can turn his mic down below like 50%, you have
to do it though, because he won't.
Alex, let me let me fix your mic when you come on. Just let me do it. Okay. Yeah
It was also in a halfway Alex and then in behavior, so don't talk disrespectfully to my my piano and my friends. Okay, Alex
Sing me a song though, Alex
What the fuck up you don't bitch
You pig you learn how to gamble in COVID. That's crazy. I've been going to casinos for 30 years
This bitch is like I learned how to gamble in COVID. You only learn poker two years ago. You fucking freak shut the fuck up
I worked really hard for my money. I was a single mom. I didn't want to hear it. You
pig bitch. Shut up. You were a single mom and you went to the casino. That's what you
did with your money. A single mother in the casino. Wow. My son is grown now. He moved
out of the house years ago. He's grown.
So you brought a casino like a hooker to gamble your savings away. What a good mom
What a good mom you are
As soon as the kids leave the house you run to the casino like a pig
Fuck up. I feel sorry for your husband
You hear me say that I learned to play poker online
I feel sorry for whoever fuck you and gave you children and that's to deal with you bitch
Okay, I'm sorry
Like what's wrong with him Alex you've got you've got him completely off the rails, haven't you I mean it's like
Road road no man, you're gonna be polite. You're gonna be polite, right?
Oh, you're the one that yells at Bita all the time, but you don't you've never yelled at me. So you're cool
I'm sorry. Just don't yell at Bita because I really like her. She's my friend
Yeah, and she we like each other Bita and I it's a back and forth. You know, I believe in her mother. She believes in herself sometimes
You give the hard love advice and sometimes it's just not wanted, you know
So sometimes it's best to give it a little bit at a time instead of you go sometimes full bore
I
Hear you, but I disagree
No, well you've done it to me to a road. No, man. You know, you've been very you know
You have a good advice, but it's like sometimes that's like
Sometimes you said sometimes if someone's gonna be in medicine
You want to take a little spoonful of like the cherry coated one and not like the whole bottle of the fucking great
Remember many months ago psyche when you were talking about social engineering
Yeah, you remember that yeah
What if I told you that I've been manipulating your relationship with reality for many months at this point and you have my
Yes, my okay, then I need you out of my life your dangerous person and yeah, let's say that kind of thing or just dangerous people
I should not have your
Bullshit, you know, and I believe he was not weak enough to fall for that anyways
And you just call you just basically called yourself out. I mean, it's like I'm just waiting for people to like stay it
Say that like you did and then I can like
I'm writing him down. I'm putting him on my spreadsheet. Your name's being crossed out of the book. I'm rogue nomad. It's like you really
You could have like, you know
Bye. Bye. You could you could have had me going like you know for years and this you know manipulated me into your heart's consent
But you know now you have no more access
stupid
People really do tell on themselves more than not.
That's right.
With psychopaths, I've studied into different things.
Psychopaths, sociopaths, and it's like the psychopaths.
Well, like social feather sometimes more careful, you know, not going to pass are a lot better at not getting caught
Psychopaths are proud of it. They want to tell on themselves
They're just like there's like but the psychopaths will have them by instead of like, oh, I'll never get caught
Oh, they'll never have those those like oh, I'm too good. I mean I'm too important
I'm too I'm too good and then it's like you know be sloppy and then it will you know, it'll be their downfall
So either like with psychopaths, so either be like maybe 30% of them are sitting on like, you know
CEOs or you know leaders of companies and a lot of different
You know like good things but half 75% of them are probably sitting in prison or in the criminal lifestyle
Actively
You know, they use it for a different
Right
Tell you that they fucking love themselves and they will put anybody in the ground
That's a good the difference is like they make they make something some people can make it legitimately using those skills to like
You know work their way up the ladder
Way I was doing it wasn't a malicious way like what if it was a humorous way?
well
You know, if I was like in like a really like good mood right now, we're like, yeah, yeah funny funny
But it's like I'm just like under a lot of stress right now, and it's like not the funniest
Time for me, but maybe like everyone else. I was fine. I don't know. Maybe
Because honestly like what yes, it could be done in a very malicious fashion
But I've done in a very humorous light hearted
Yeah, but then
influence on psyche. Sorry bud. You are nobody. Okay. Well,
just so you know, I'm not in his chat, but he doesn't know it. I
don't. Okay. Well, I'm gonna, I'm not everybody tonight except
for, um, you know, Electra and Jamie's Cowboys and we'll see
what happens after that for you. Okay. Unless you're one of
them, you're a shit out of luck. Okay. So, he's he's telling
you he has an all in your chat that he's saying he's an all to
my mind and he's saying that he's been messing with my mind
for months and but then he's been diffusing
The impact of that statement, but the humor which is what the humor is
No, no, it's not but it's a distraction. Oh, it's like the it's like a diffuser. It's like oh, it's like just like Jim
It's using it is your humor in an evil way, right?
But don't you think that you put yourself in a very vulnerable position by why to be a targeted by asses like you know, go away
Thank you
No, no, no
It was my fault. I put myself in a vulnerable position. It wasn't it wasn't people trying to like, you know
It was just me putting myself in a vulnerable position, but I'm vulnerable, I'm just putting
myself all out there.
A lot of people have everybody in their chat modded and it goes a certain way.
Here it didn't go that way, you know, all you can do is freaking learn from your experiences
and that's what you're doing.
It was kind of funny.
Come up here and say that he's an alt and he got a mod in your chat as an alt like
Yeah, it's probably just to annoy me
Rogue nomad, what's your alt's name? Yeah, tell me your mom also I can
Probably not. Just kidding. I have no control.
Everybody I have no control over stream yard. Okay, I give up all my commands on my command station battleship
I know he's bullshit, but I just said, you know, it's not really funny. It's either right now
Then he does it again. It's like, I was just like, you know, it's just like that. It's like it didn't there joke to the land
Right. It's like if you try to be funny and like, you know, make any of that or he's trying to like make people uncomfortable
Yeah, that guy is a narcissist. Oh my god up here. He makes it about himself
But he acts like he's trying to give advice to other people, but it's all about him. Oh
It's also the advice is like mansplaining or it's like a very condescending or
Marmy kind of oh, let me tell you the world works. Okay. I know everything. You don't know shit
Yeah, yeah, I'm in control. I've been manipulating in mind for months. Okay. I mean your mom in your chat isn't out
This is what you're present. It's just make it. This makes my skin crawl. Like, uh, I
Never liked it. Yeah, I know
I mean
That's why that's why he has the muscles. I mean, it's like I'm such a simp for these stupid muscles
Yeah, I don't know. There's like this thing about the shape of the reminds me of like Eric the Midget's balloons
Even though you're gay you really are a man still. I mean, that's good
But also it's like you guys are very driven by your physical attraction, huh?
But that's also the whole reason behind like the the whole
You know transgenders like the attraction to transgenders is because they are these masters of illusion and they have
And it's just like in women too are you know women many many many women that stereotyping are good at the
Arts of makeup and fashion and you know presentation. Oh, yeah
But this is actually more important to men than to women.
We're in a way, so plastic surgery.
So, so narcissists, you have to be a little bit narcissistic to survive in the California and it's like it's just because everybody comes from everywhere in the world to be something somebody to be a star here, and it's so hard and it's like, I was born here, I was born into this bullshit.
So yeah, I don't have a narcissistic bone in my body.
We just took I just took a narcissistic test the other day because I was giving it to my co host and to Casey and he scored like eight out of 44.
I think I scored five out of 44 so it was super low, but
It was just yeah, it's interesting. Well, I think they're not it is a spectrum
Right. Narcissists will tell you they'd be like they want to get 44 out of 44. Yeah.
True Narcissists would know how to get the
Either like a either like a zero score or the perfect score. I mean they're they're gonna know how to
But because they're compulsive liars most of the time too. Yeah
They they can compulsively lie and often they'll say they're empathetic because empathy and
Narcissism are kind of like two sides of a coin and so they will
Think that they have empathy. Oh, it's like it's like a dark and they protect dark empath
It's like the others they actually they can like because it's like it's like a kind of a chameleon
They can they can like see somebody crying
They see somebody crying and they can like cry to because they see the person crying and they can all act like they
But then it's like there's nothing really there. They are there just they're doing it
It's called dark empathy because you're using your the emotion to manipulate the other person the thinking you're but then it's like
You're trying to manipulate the mirror
People really well. Yeah, I'm mirroring mirroring. So mirroring makes people very comfortable with them and yeah
Oh, because it's okay. Here's the thing about that is like when you mirror somebody really well
You're reflecting their qualities and so they end up falling in love with themselves through your yours
You just put in the mask of them and then it's like and then they fall in love with themselves in you
And it's like they're you falling in love with themselves, but they think you're falling in love with you
It's very confusing. I'm sorry. I mean
you had a great point. I've said a lot about narcissism because you know I know. I'm minor in psychology when I was in nursing school. It fascinates me. And it doesn't really, I don't know. I just, I'm very empathetic. And so I really relate to people. But I also want to know what's going on with the people that are
Bad actors and are trying to harm other people because I don't think like that
I don't get it. And so it it fucks with my head
And I I've fallen prey to it a couple times and I'm old enough now that I think that I wouldn't but you know
Who knows?
But you know what like why we think fall like why we we're okay, so we've had like
We had a good example. We had a good example of people in our life. And so we've been able to like
We haven't been like we might have had had everyone's been hurt in their life, but I think some of these people have been so hurt
that it's like, they turn, they're like, their empathy turns off for other people, and maybe for themselves, and they, instead of, because there's something called the Wounded Healer, you can look at mythology, the Wounded Healer,
Kairon got, he got an arrow shot at him by Hercules, and it was by a special arrow, and even though Kairon was immortal, he had his wound, and so he was immortal, but with his painful wound, and so he could never heal.
Through the story of his pain or whatever
But and some people are the opposite that they are some hurt people hurt people or hurt people
One you know how bad it feels and he'll I grew up hurt
Not like I I have a I've told people this for I have
a Los Angeles syndrome I have a college in disorder and I
Grew up in the hospital like in pain and it's not what did I do? I said
could help children that are in the hospital so I became a nurse and I worked
it with adults until I got good enough and then I went and worked at the
pediatric hospital because I know I could understand what they were going
through nobody ever asked me like what are you going through this really sucks
you're in here all the time like
That was really fucking blow. You know, I just wanted someone to ask me and nobody ever did they just were like, okay
Here's your discharge paperwork spy
You know and it's very difficult like especially when you get to the end of life
Kind of hospice stuff or and we're doing with from people with terminal illnesses. They told me terminal illnesses. I
Mean, this is very of course is like horrible for the family to deal with and there's all these kind of things that the nurses are
Just really these angels that step in
With like no judgment and like with like, you know, smile happy and it is really
Take they take a look the big burden off the family from the families
That doesn't really know what to do the family can sometimes it's like the person is
Say the if it's hard for the family sometimes to see the person in that state
And it's hardest for the families because the person that's dying is ready to go. Usually it's hardest for the families
Yeah, rogue. No mad you're right. I will keep a wall up here and I'll be this character. Denison's a little circle
Okay, many people are little fucking circles Alexander never cams up most people never came up
I'm a cartoon. I think it's a little more interactive than being a circle, which I don't care. It'd be a circle
But yeah, I will keep a wall up for people like you
You exactly if I had a cartoon I would use
Yeah, I would be an orange tabby cat
Yeah, I mean I can change into different cartoons you like there's a really hilarious thing if look look at a player
it's called like look a cat zoom call and so this it was like there's this like a
Oh yeah, he had a cat.
The filter got turned into the cabby cat on his Zoom call.
He's like, huh, Judge?
I can't seem to change the filter.
Yeah, it's like a little cat talking like this.
I can be a cat, too.
And yeah, I will keep a wall up, Rogue, because there are people like you.
And um, there's no need for me to let my wall down for people like rogue nomad
Okay, so now we have oji vato is in the backstage. So oji vato. I have a room that you're alex
I mean is he man here guys is oji vato out? I have to hear after you first of all, I'll put a banner
Oji vato is this you
Okay, I don't think it doesn't sound like Alex, but hey
You're not Alex. Okay. This is okay. Is your name is your name Romeo blues by the way
Electrum I get that joke election. We'll get that that's Eric images alias that he used on on a
certain kind of work
Right now. Um, oh you are yeah
Oh, where's that?
Was that what's up tonight? Tell me now. Yeah, Alex. Do I come up and say hi? Oh gee you can't but you can't call
Electro bitch or call me any names or anything you have to be if you kind but I'll let you back up to say hi to him because I know
Yeah
So good
Okay
A lot of my food comes back, but that is not what a penis looks like. You are so right
It looks like a gooey duck. It's the closest thing that they have on here
I don't think a strawberry got put through like the stretching machine
If your penis looks like that you got to see a doctor
And if it can talk
Oh my god, that's it. That's I heard John. Probably what Alex is going through right now.
Yeah, Alex. Alex, what happened to your penis, Alex? Oh, here comes Alex.
Is he just talking to you when he's purple? No, I ain't here, Alex.
Me and my hero, G, what you want, homie? What you want, young stuff?
Want some smoke?
You know, I always want to smoke motherfucker
People's podcast aspect for you belong
What are you doing here shit
Follow me around guys. Don't don't fight. Please. Are you supposed to be friends? Oh, we're gonna fight. Thank you
unfortunately
No, so I'll go to the bathroom or go take a bike ride because we're gonna fight it
So if you don't like it then shut your eyes and shut the fuck up
What's up?
My show I can't hear you
Oh
No
Put Alex back up there. Let's go
He says he said I said this is my show he said not anymore and so it's like I don't feel like having me
I'll put them up there for two minutes
He ran from the studio crying like a bitch you don't sound like a pyro
Alex knows what it is. Yeah, I destroyed him many times before my face
Alex just needs to go to a hooker and do some blow and calm down for a little bit, okay?
He just needs to whack off and get his hands on my face. He don't want no smoke
Well, I I do but I'm a big smoker. Yeah, it's okay
Hookers and blow psyche is treat
Sorry
Listen
After two minutes, it'll be all good. He'll know what it is. Yeah, I'll just take a little take a copy do a line of coke
The People's Podcast. What's The People's Podcast, OG?
Oh, yeah, that's what I thought. I thought I had met you there, but I met you on a different panel.
The People's Podcast is a panel where they talk...
I mean, there's a lot of auditors on there, and they talk a lot about current events and things like that.
They have a big panel. It's one of the first panels that I would go on and do some readings on.
Really?
Everyone's pretty nice there, but then there's the guy in there.
I don't I would just heard of him in my chat people were mentioning. Oh, I think oh jevon says Alex and I
Kind of the same thing
Yeah, they're not the same person yeah now we know guys
No, you don't even have the same accent
You don't have to tell me but I'm gonna ask where you from
Part of the country north south east west. What kind of an accent do you think I had?
Australian or New Zealand
Denizen
Denizen, yeah
What kind of accent do you think I have? Oh, you're American? Oh my god. I'm way off. I'm sure
It's a sound Australian is when you said just making that one up right there. Oh, you are
You know I might it's cool. It's okay. What's the crikey?
I could I could guess where OG is from but
OG I'd say
Where am I from?
Chicago?
Chicago or New York?
No, he's not
No, not Chicago, not New York
Florida?
He's from California
One more guess
I'll give you one more guess
Nevada, Las Vegas
California
Las Vegas
Nope
Okay, I got it wrong
Michigan
Where you live in California?
No
Okay, talk for it. Can we let him talk for 20 seconds?
Fuck how to get all quiet
Really talk go ahead and talk with you about it. Let's hear your voice. No, we got all quiet for a minute. But yeah, go ahead continue
Okay, yeah moving subjects changing subjects, um
the
Oh, I don't I could have guessed that okay, so there are things okay, so I was gonna say people's podcast
It's okay
So whatever that there's a guy named Michael Bruno there and he was just a two-faced like he I gave him a reading and
Then I just he just talked a lot of shit about me after everywhere else is really nice from there
I think I'm at I think I'm at summer there
Maybe and you know some other people that come to my show now summer has to talk to his channel and she also has
I
Tell me Alex, okay, listen I hear the Alex
He's he's faking it and it's not Alex
Anything like Alex
That's exactly what Alex would say if he was pretending to be somebody else. No, it's not
Do I actually sound like Alex? Are you saying that?
We're just on the panel at the same time. We heard them speak at the same time and they're nothing the same
Well lecture, that's the thing about this new world is like, you know, you can you can have
But do I actually sound like Alex my my
People that's how I heard Richard Christie and sound
Do those do those two to the four voices on the phone pretty well, so you guess you can
And you don't speak like him either. You don't flip out
At least I mean
Come up with different
Profiles or voices whatever I I don't even want I don't even want to expect you
He was banned on my chat for about a month's time and he was still here every day, so.
I don't know why I'm so curious about you, Oji Bato. I'm curious about you.
I don't know. What's your name? What's your name?
DJ Electra.
Can't say I've come across you, but I don't know. Why are you curious? Tell me now.
Don't know you just have like a presence about you since you came up here
You've calmed in a world where most people get up here and they're calling and they're complete assholes
And they just go off the handle
He came up here yelling and screaming expletives. Oh far. He's been pretty cool
Sometimes well, sometimes calm is like a quiet anger
I always worry about calm people quiet calm my peeps. Is that what I got here?
No quiet quiet quiet anger like a calm calm voice can be like a very
Very person that's very controlled emotions that there could be like a see this is like chicks get with serial killers
They're not good right right analyzing personalities. No, no, that's the thing
Calm down
Okay, I'm just gonna be quiet about that's what he said to me
What do you say I was already up here the other night when beta and rainy were like
My lesting you they they were pretending to be cop psyche. Were you here?
You know you were sleeping psych and they were pretend like that went on for about
Three hours innocent. What'd you say?
Oh, I don't I don't know it went on a little too long. It started off
Being fun, and then it got kind of gay and I couldn't come up because I would have come up
But I couldn't because like then we could have you say you're kind of gay or yeah
But you don't forget when it's one girls pretending to be cops
And they were arresting Dennis and it just went on to a little too long
But like I was gonna come up and make it a full-blown orgy. I think you need more people at least have an orgy like
With three chick cops in you, Denizen, would you?
I mean, that's kind of a little scary though.
Well, Denizen, what if it's two female cops,
including DJ Electra, and then there's
one hot male cop that might be me, or Alex?
What about that?
No, no, I think you're cute, but I'm too straight.
OK.
Well, I would just stand in the corner
and then take pictures.
I would okay, I know
Alexander you old you rocked on my peeps. I'm not gonna lie if it like if you're a heart
Are you a hot cartoon avatars involved? I'm down. Let's do it. There we go
Let's have this interrogation. Okay. I can turn guys by every day. I turn at least one guy by every day
I look a little bit like my cartoon like maybe I don't know
10% like my cartoon
I think the personality comes through it. The personality comes through it with the
Expressions to it. I mean it's like and so that kind of transforms
Whatever it looks like if you have the personality coming through that's a that's a whole other aspect of yourself
Well, hey sake you take the expressions in the AI comes through
Well, it's like, you know, it's getting better and better, you know, it's not it's like so, you know, it's so just it's programs
But it's program by AI though. This is just a facial recognition. So it shows but
DJ Electra, do you think that?
What your AI
avatar
Expresses comes
Comes through is what you're trying to get through to the audience
Um a lot of the time. Yeah, I mean like right now. I'm smiling right now. I put my my eyebrows
Smiling her eyebrows up and so it's expressive, but I actually watched this uh, I don't know. I look angry
Oh, no, that's Botox. I put some Botox on because sometimes my eyebrows were going too
Do you think that DJ?
This technology is from before AI
Do you think that your AR emoji?
Brings across what you're trying to express as a real thing that oh in a purple circle brings across what you're trying to express
No
I don't, but I'm not, I don't have an emoji that moves and talks and speaks
I think mine's a little bit closer than a circle, but it's not
Even, even I, I have a human body and even
I have a circle, you don't want my circle on page, come on
It looks like, it looks like a big zero
I wish it said OG
I watch a show, or I watch a show, I watch a commentary show, and it's called My Thoughts,
My T.H.O.C.S.
And this woman...
I've heard what she looks like. She said she's like a heavy set Asian woman or whatever
But she has her avatars. It's a potato a talking potato with a wig like a little like a shiny wig
I used to be a packet of french fries. Yeah
The personality comes to that so much of your personality is your boy. I mean a lot of expression, but you're dealing with like
Yeah, that's kind of what I'm asking. I'm just asking if she feels like
Not even what she looks like
Just her expressions, if she thinks her expressions come by in that emotion.
They are pretty close.
I have limited my eye movement because my eyes would sometimes dart around too much.
Um, and it was like distracting for people. They were like your eyes are wiggin out. So, uh, I did get some Botox in my
cartoon eyes
Yeah
Yeah, a lot of it is
pretty spot-on
It's like it's like almost like you know grand theft auto you create an avatar and you can create what the avatars hair looks like you can create
Well, you know you're with the body and you can be very specific with avatar. Is this
Represent you as you really in any way
It gets maybe close as it can get in this video game atmosphere, but it's like, you know, you're not going to match real life, you know, you know, but I mean, and I've shown people pictures of myself and I've been on camera on other panels before so it's not I just I choose them.
I choose not to have.
Interactions with people like that one guy that was on here before that frickin. What's his name? I can't remember
Rogue no matter whatever who's they're just shady and they're they don't have good intentions and
Women get a lot of shit
Yes, it's true, it's true, and that's you know, you know, I have a he-man the chat
I don't hope I don't reveal too much, but he-man was getting harassed as you know under a he-man's real name and so
He man who is as they have said in the chat many times. They are a woman, but they were the he-man and I got and
The weirdos leave him alone. Like, you know, they have a very strong masculine name. And so it's like, you know
Yeah, the mask we wear can be you know the mask sometimes our defense mechanism. Okay, Alex sir
I was your behavior self. I asked you keep coming back up. What are you doing?
Are you okay? Are you okay? Cuz you look like you're on crack
He's stressed out literally no, I never seen sight you see him
We wakes up after a nap. He's all calm and looking around for the pipe right now the motherfuckers and shut up for two hours straight
He's shaking like a crackin. He's on drugs
Dude, you're so projecting
Dude, bitch, shut up shut up. I run are you fat pig psyche?
Don't you fucking small and we can all see through it. It's a bad look though. He thinks that we can see Alexander
You're a bad. Alex. Alex, please Alex, please
Alex you are having hallucinations of like
some some like some kind of
Brigade dresses and three muskets here's
You know with Gotti as the coffee boy and rain as the head of it and
Everybody else is involved everybody basically except for me
You know, I'm the only person even I think you're involved in it now. Are you in there? Are you in the are you in the
What's it called the grotto? I don't know what it's called the
I've been there get a brigade. Hey, hey, we have I was outside the fence
Is a better guest than Alex
Did you just call me a coffee boy?
No, I said that's what Alice Alice in the discord grotto
Rain runs it and then you know JT's you know her second command and you're just like the coffee the coffee boy
You like basically drive the ice cream truck and like
No, that was serious, I see I thought you're the head of the I thought you were the head of the
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't
What's up? Oh, Alex. Hold on.
your god, how you doing man?
what's going on?
yeah, I'm good
how are you?
he's quiet, man
how's it going?
what's going on?
how are you?
told me the other day
he can't shit
wait
he needed a fucking
he needed a fucking shit
I'm destroying you
tell me now
do you want me to go or do you need a stick head?
he's always putting my business up there
I don't know what's going on with this guy
Okay, we have another guest guys. Let's welcome J-Dog to the chat.
J-Dog, J-Dog, what's up?
What's up, psyche? What's up, people?
He's part of that death cult. How's your death cult doing, J-Dog?
Do you have a skull?
Technically Christianity is a death cult because look at them. They worship Jesus on a cross
Yes, I mean, I'm telling I'm telling God because you just know what the ultimate God
God you're being blasphemous
You're being blasphemous you need to spell your name with the lower case of G because I think so
What the real God is
God God considers you like Lucifer right now
Yeah
And then there's a lot in the chat you and J dogs in the chat
That's total. Maybe there's God because I see GOD back or it's a God J. Yeah
The guy sitting here
You know what it is on down what oh what oh chill
Yeah, bro, we just be chilling all day. I didn't say gay. I didn't think it was this motherfucking chill and he just chill
All right, I don't have to yell to get my point across
I'll read the Bible later
I don't have any tattoos. No, it's too bad. God. I do God. Do you ever see my school tattoo? You have one? Yeah, I've seen that actually. Yeah, you saw it. Yeah. Sure. The one the girl on the back is better though. That's the best one you got. Oh, yeah. I mean, that's the OG, but there's a cool, but it's a bad attitude, so I've never seen that one actually psyche. I like it. Oh, Electra, you love that one.
the
Yeah
I'll believe that the stories in the Bible are real life were real life or do you believe that they are parables for?
You know learning
Parables
He said he speaks in parables and Jesus said things were taught in parables and he was kind of telling trying to tell you
Don't think the Bible's so literally just like you're saying he's like I'm not actually got I'm part of God
You can watch the father through me, but you're also all part of God like every all of us have this to do
Me as the new God of the world
Oh my gosh, well goddamn it God
It's like a lot of people really really really believe in science, but they've never seen an atom at it
You know sure state. It's it's smallest state
They've never seen a lot of science with their eyes a lot of people haven't seen the Bible or the stories or the past
From the Bible with their own eyes
So it's like there's belief in both that you have to have faith in either one
I'll stop talking now. I know if you ever heard of the Lima, you know, Alistair Crowley and he was like a very big
You know, he not a lot of people may know about him, but he's probably one of the biggest influences on like
And the entertainment industry and just the way things are he predicted like there to be this big it's called the Asia
You wrote you wrote some books
The equinox is all about uniting of the science and the religion that's what he
you wanted to do, you wanted to, you wanted to start.
So he's like, it's human spirituality,
but make it very scientific.
And, okay, go ahead and I'll go sing over me, go ahead.
It's okay. I'm just kidding. Okay, so yeah
he went he went he said I think the equinox says it's like the method of
Science the aim of religion and it's like it's supposed it's like uniting the two because they are they're kind of on the duality
And he always believes in like the alchemy of like putting
It's like the father energy the mother energy, which are these two separate energies putting them together that creates a child
It's a whole new world, right? And so
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry
I didn't do anything with the video. This is just for the music part
It's not reggae, it's reggae, man.
Composal that's not a radio bass line. That's not even a bass line
Coming out
I'm not saying that I am a premiere music producer I am not
that is this I got on band lab and I taught myself how to do that
and I just said fuck I'm gonna learn how to do it because I was making AI music which is fun
but I'd rather you know produce my own music and um I'm gonna do it with her I can or not
what did you produce in that song
baseline she said that she did some of the vocals and
the bass line the vocals I mix the vocal these there's like two words but what what did you
produce in the actual song the vocals I recorded and I I put all the I put all the drums in there
I put I played the bass line I wrote that and yeah
So she's basically like a you know, I got a female mr. Big Pipe for the thousand times better
Okay, Tyler Tyler remember happened last time he didn't go too well Tyler
No, yeah, would you rather say that? Yeah
You're saying that I stole music
Are you backing up your claim are you claiming that you did not tell me no
Anybody on the musical scale does anybody on the musical?
Samples that I used our samples is called stealing
Is not stealing oh gee
That looks like a smoker, but actually, oh, there he goes. Oh, he's a smoker. You want to believe him before me? I'm just, uh...
Talk about me
What are you talking about
You're drunk. You're drunk.
Hey, thank you. Hey, thank you.
I wrote a song. Do you want to
see it?
Tyler, you're drunk. You're drunk.
Drink in the big beer.
Drink in the big beer with the fake chain.
Hell yeah.
Play my song.
Play my fucking song.
Wow
Are you okay Tyler? Who sent you over here Tyler?
Who thinks you over here?
Who thinks you over here though somebody's over here a valid point and the valid point is
That one guy that you had up here is a classic moron.
He looks like my kid.
Are you my
Lotto this your boy
No, it's your woman
He's wearing a fucking bracelet he asked me a question
Where'd you get that chain where'd I get this yeah, I got it from team
I
Like you gotta let psyche know how to order off to move because he was trying the last time order something off team
Who and it kept like having him spin the wheel and we don't want him to get scammed
DJ Electra
Would you date this
Tyler looks younger than my son
You look like Alex's daughter
Yeah, I'll take care of people.
Alright, shut the fuck up with your delay.
You homo, get the fuck out of here.
I don't know.
Get the delay too.
Get your gay ass out of here, man.
That chain's gotta go, Tyler.
It's gotta go.
Homo, okay.
Get your ass out of here, man.
He's obviously underage, like, you don't know why he's here.
That was a gate to
Go back to tick-tock
Smoking Virginia slams you a bitch. Get out of here. Take your ass out of here. You're a bitch
Take that cigarette with you
Let's take that cigarette up your ass. You fucking dumbass
Fuck up, Oprah
all
I
Tyler so no one really sent you over here you just came on your own
Yeah
He never really comes around this this this section of YouTube that's always like
I'm just like trying to figure out like if somebody like push up to like
hold on one second one second one second
walls my babes
get your ass out of here nigga
no actually what basically got me over here
you got the classic
basement walls my babes
you work for Q
no nobody hears you
don't you
oh Q has the games here
no you just gay
so so so so gay
dude
He's a grease ball. You're just gay, my baby. You're just gay
With the pan on the wall
Look at that nail, look at that nail, look at that fucking nail, that was the worst, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, burn the stream, burn the stream, burn the stream, burn the fucking stream, burn the stream, burn the stream, burn the whole stream, burn the whole stream, burn the whole stream, burn the whole stream, burn the whole stream, burn the whole stream, burn the whole stream, burn the whole stream, burn the whole stream, burn the whole stream, burn the whole stream, burn the whole stream, burn the whole stream, burn the whole stream, burn the whole stream, burn the whole stream, burn the whole stream, burn the whole stream, burn the whole stream, burn the whole stream, burn the whole stream, burn the whole stream, burn the whole stream, burn the whole stream, burn the whole stream, burn the whole stream, burn the whole stream, burn the whole stream, burn the whole stream, burn the whole stream, burn the whole stream, burn the whole stream, burn the whole stream,
Take it down dude. Don't be a homo man. Just get the fuck about it